Please, let's rise up as we worship our
God,
Lord. We worship you.
Thank you, Jesus. [music]
You are good. You are good.
Oh
[singing]
yeah. [music]
Oh [singing] Lord,
my God, [singing]
all that I want
is your touch. [music and singing]
My faith
[music] is hiding
on this [singing] mountain.
So drink from you, oh Lord.
Raise your hands and say, "Oh Lord,
[music and singing]
my God,
all that I want
is your [music and singing] touch.
My faith
is hiding
on this mountain [music]
to drink from your Lord. [singing]
[music]
Yes.
[singing]
No one [music] say [singing]
[music]
[music and singing]
Oh.
Oh. [singing and music]
[music and singing]
Oh.
Oh. [singing]
Lord.
>> My [singing and music]
God.
I want,
>> oh God, I want
is [music and singing] your
>> my
[music and singing]
[music]
God.
>> My God. He's
[music]
the
>> mighty. [music]
He is
on this mountain
to drink from your
[music]
>> [music]
>> water
and
[music] you
are [singing]
thor. [music]
My God,
you
are
just
[music]
Power
is [music]
wonder.
[music]
[singing]
You say what you say.
>> Say [music and singing]
what you say.
[music]
>> Say what you say. [singing]
is the one.
[music]
>> You are my father
and my
mighty God.
You are [singing]
my God.
You are my father
and my
mighty God. You are my God. I am the
mighty ever God
as good as you. I have never ever seen
God [music]
God
as good as you.
I have never seen a God as good as you.
[music] You are my Lord
and my defender.
Almighty [music] God, [singing]
you are my king.
[music] You are my lover
and my [music] sustainer. [singing]
Almighty God, you are [singing]
my [music] Lord. I have never ever seen
your God
as good as you. I have never ever
[music] seen a God
as good as you. I have never ever seen
[music] God
as good as you. I have never ever seen.
Oh [singing and music] God has good
God. [singing]
[music]
>> Oh God,
[music] my Lord my own. You're so
mindful.
>> So,
>> so mindful [music]
of me,
[music]
>> my
[music] mindful.
>> I have never
>> I have never ever seen [music] God.
>> I [music] have never
>> I have never ever seen
I
will never ever [music]
I am never ever God.
[music]
>> I have never
>> I have never ever seen your
hallelujah.
I am never ever
[music]
>> I have never ever seen
>> [singing]
>> God as good [music]
as you.
>> You are my father
and my sustainer.
Almighty God. You are my God.
You are my fathery.
My sustainer,
almighty [screaming]
God.
You are my God.
All my lover, [singing]
all defender, [music]
almighty God.
You are my God.
All our protector,
Almighty God,
you are my Lord. I would never ever see.
Oh God
as good as you. I will never ever see.
[music] Oh [singing] God
as good as you.
>> Good God. Good God.
Good God. [singing]
Good.
My Lord, [music] my Lord, my own. You're
so mindful. So, you're so mindful
[music]
[singing] of me.
Good God.
Good God. [music]
Good God. Oh, [singing]
my God. My God. My God. You are so
mindful. [music]
You're soful.
Love. Let me hear you scream.
>> It's time to give God all the praise.
I believe you came with your dancing
shoes. Oh yeah. Come on.
The Lord is good
and all the time.
Hey.
[music]
Hey. Come on. To the left, to the right.
Oh. Oh, that man will praise the Lord.
Oh, that man will praise the Lord.
For his goodness, his wonderful works
with the children of men. With the
children of men [music] for his goodness
for his wonderful works to the children
of men. To the children of
[music and singing] men. He has broken
that shade of
that thunder.
He has broken that [music] g of
the back of
[music]
we praise the Lord.
We praise the Lord for the goodness of
[music] his wonderful
children to the children of goodness
[music]
to the children of the children.
The grace [music] of God
[music]
coming again. Oh, that man will praise
the [music and singing] Lord. Oh, that
man will praise the Lord
for his goodness and for [music] his
wonderful work. To the children of men.
To the children of men. for his goodness
and for his wonderful work. To the
children of men, to the children of men,
he has broken the gate of
the iron.
He has broken the [music] gate of
[music] We will praise the Lord.
>> We will praise the Lord. We praise the
Lord.
Our [music] God is wonderful to the
children of men to the children of man.
[music]
He is wonderful to the children of the
children of God. He has the head [music]
of God.
>> He has the [music] head of [singing]
God.
>> That is why we say you are good and your
mercy is forever. [music and singing]
>> Hallelujah.
>> You are good and your mercy is forever.
>> Hallelujah. [music and singing]
Jesus, you are good and your mercy is
forever.
>> Hallelujah.
>> You are [music] good and your mercy is
forever.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Oh, you are so good and your mercy is
forever.
>> Hallelujah.
>> You [music] are so good and your mercy
is forever.
>> Hallelujah. [music]
Oh, do you mind?
Do you mind?
Do you
[music]
[music and singing]
>> My healer.
You are my
>> my
[music]
proider
provider. [music]
provider.
Hey,
let the nations sing. Let the people
glory. [music]
Let your kingdom come for your spirit
house. Let the nation sing. Let the
nation sing.
>> Let the nation [music] sing. Let the
people shout.
>> Let the kingom come.
>> Let the [music] kingdom come for your
Let the nation sing a shout to the Lord.
>> Let the nation [music] sing. Let the
people shout.
Let the king of God, oh Lord,
>> let the king of God [music] pour your
spirit.
>> Let the nation sing. Let the nation
sing.
>> Let [music] the nation sing. Let people
come. Come on, sing. Come on, sing. Oh,
let the kingom come. [music]
>> Let the kingom come for his
reason [music] to praise
the Lord. [singing]
Oh my soul. [music]
>> Oh my soul.
Praise
the Lord, oh my soul. I found a reason
to praise
[music]
the Lord, oh my [singing] soul.
>> Praise the Lord.
The Lord, oh my God, I praise [music]
the Lord, oh my soul.
>> Oh, praise.
The [music] love of my soul.
>> Tell me God
every day you walk. You come through for
me.
I have no
Lord. You came through for me.
Every day you come. You come through for
me.
I have no and I know Lord you came to me
oh
for
[music]
a well
in every situation.
condition. You must let the go.
>> In every situation, [music]
condition
[music]
>> in every situation
condition you must speak.
In every situation,
condition
[music]
you must learn to Because [music]
>> in every situation,
you must let the speaker
[music] come alive. [screaming]
[music]
>> I am breaker.
>> I am.
>> I am breaker. I am [music] breaker.
>> I am breaker.
>> Iron breaker.
>> The [music] chain breaker.
>> I am breaker.
Jehovah. [music]
>> I am breaker. Oh je.
>> I am breaker.
>> I am break.
>> He breaks everything.
>> I am breaker. I am breaker.
>> I am breaker.
>> I [music] am breaker.
[music]
[singing]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Come on.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yummy yummy [music] yummy yummy yummy
yummy yummy [singing]
yummy yummy yummy.
>> [music]
>> We say
hey
I
am [music]
here I am. Here I am. Hey,
hey, [singing] I am [music] free. Oh.
Oh. Hey,
hey,
hey. [music]
[music]
Hey I am here I am. Hey I [music] am
here [singing] I am.
[music]
>> [music]
>> la.
[music]
>> [music and singing]
>> Say
[music]
[singing]
>> we praise the Lord
above.
The king
of [music] glory.
[music]
>> For the Lord
of all,
the king above.
[singing]
[music]
He said, [music]
[singing]
Oh
[music and singing]
lae.jah.
[music]
[singing]
Yahe [music]
say
yahe
>> the lord
of lord
the king
of glory
yahe
The Lord
of God
begin to
note
very long
>> [singing]
>> Can we begin to lift up our voice and
engage this atmosphere?
>> [music]
>> is the pioneers conference and we are
pioneers.
>> [snorts]
>> Build up yourself on your most holy
faith.
We have come to engage. We have come to
encounter Jesus.
We have come to Zion.
Ashanti. ASHANTI. ASHANTI. ASHI.
WOULD
you engage this morning
that the street might be open? [music]
That the script might be open.
SO
[music]
is you and Jesus this morning.
>> [music]
>> And the ENCOUNTER CAN HAPPEN NOW. AND
THE ENCOUNTER CAN NOW
JESUS.
You can be tired now.
Oh father, we thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> Do not look left nor right. Do not look
left nor right. Do not look left nor
right. But look unto Jesus.
It is him we have COME TO EXPERIENCE.
IT IS FREE.
It is only him that can open it. It is
only him that can open it. It is only
him that can open it. It is only him
that can open it.
Sh
up.
[music]
It's not performance. It's not
performance. It's not performance.
The water is dead. The water is dead.
Can you die?
Father, we thank you.
Father, we thank you. [music]
Father, we thank you. Can you just in a
minute just thank God
for such a wonderful presence? [music]
Lord, we give you praise.
Lord, we give you praise. Soak it in
because much more is coming. Soak it in
because much more is coming.
Amen.
>> Amen.
Can you welcome someone by your left, by
your right? Um it's scriptton scrolls.
This is the parinas conference. Welcome,
welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome,
welcome, welcome, welcome. Yeah, we are
king sword, please. Welcome. All right,
let us have our seats.
All right, so it's um
it's script scrolls and this is the
second edition of
>> the paras conference. Are we excited?
>> Are we excited?
And this particular edition, it's uh
themed script and scrolls.
And um
we all know that every move of God
begins with what he has already spoken.
And so what that means is that the Bible
will be open, revelation will be seen,
and lives will be touched. This morning,
I I just want you to you know prepare
your heart you know get your writing
materials um ensure that your heart is
ready for what is to come and the Lord
will bless you in Jesus name um if you
need to use the restroom it is by my
left right here and um
and um if if you also need uh certain
things please speak to the ushers um and
the Lord will bless you in Jesus name
all right I think my my work is done
here. Um,
so let me just
Okay.
Okay. All right. So, please, um, a
welcome video will be on my screen. Um,
and that's by MID. And as soon as that
is done, the next voice you will be
hearing will be PMID. Praise God.
Welcome to
the Pioneers Conference. Once again, God
bless you.
>> Hello, pioneers. It's my joy and
excitement to welcome you to the
pioneers conference [music] 2026 and it
is themed script and scroll. Remember as
Kingswood we have no taste for me
religion without change. One of the
reasons we have put this conference
together, especially the script and
school, is to bring to your clarity, is
to bring to your understanding that
which was written about you before the
foundation of the world, so that you can
lead this conference [music]
and step out there into your community,
into your space, being the trained agent
[music] that you are pioneering great
and mighty things. Again, I'll remind
you our second line of the Kingswood
creed that you have no taste for me
religion without change. [music] Now, as
I begin to round up, before I go off
stage, you know, teaching in this
conference, I want to put to you that
part [music] of the things that was
written about you before the foundation
of the world is the fact that you're an
envoy. You are a kingdom representative.
You have been sent to your space, to
your community to bring hope where there
is darkness, to bring clarity where
there is confusion, to bring excellence
where there is mediocrity. That is why
you are where you [music] are at the
moment. And we are here today in this
conference to help you realize this to
help you come to the clarity honest
understanding of that which was written
about [music] you before the foundation
of the world. And it is my joy to
welcome you to the pioneers conference
[music] 2026 script and scroll. Thank
you.
You are that answer to this darkness.
Somebody say, "I'm the answer."
We have young people in this house now.
>> Say, "I'm the answer."
>> The darkness Nigeria is facing. Say it.
The darkness Nigeria is facing. The
darkness Africa is facing, the darkness
covering the world right now. I am the
answer. Say, I am the answer. Say it
like you know it. I am the answer. You
are that answer. That's the title of
this teaching and I have very few
moments and I want you to pay attention.
Can we read this scripture together?
Isaiah chapter 60. Popular scripture.
Isaiah chapter 60. Projector. Can you
help me? I mean projection. Help me.
Isaiah 60 from verse 1 to 7. I want us
to read together. Projection. I'm
waiting for you. My scripture is here.
Or should we go without them? I think we
should do without them so that they
don't they don't hold us back. If you
are there, Isaiah chapter 60, we are
reading for from verse 1 to 7. Can we
read it together? One to go. Arise. Come
on, let's read together everybody.
Arise, shine, for thy light has come,
and the glory of the Lord is risen upon
thee. Verse two, for behold, the
darkness shall cover the earth, and
gross darkness the people, but the Lord
shall arise upon thee, and his glory
shall be seen upon thee. Verse three,
Read louder.
>> Verse four. Lift up thine eyes round
about and see. All they gather
themselves together. They come to thee.
Thy sons shall come from far and thy
daughters shall be nursed at thy side.
Verse five. Then thou shalt see and flow
together and thine eye shall fear and be
enlared because the abundance of the sea
shall be converted unto thee. The forces
of the gent gentiles shall come unto
thee. Verse six. The multitude of camel
shall come. Can we read it together? The
drums of Midian and Epha, all the all
the from Seb shall come. They shall
bring gold and incense, and they shall
show forth the praise. Verse seven,
carry together. All the flocks of cave
shall be gathered together unto who? The
rams of neighbor shall minister unto
thee. They shall come up with acceptance
on my altar. And now we glorify the
house.
Can we celebrate God for those words? We
can do better. How kings youth, can we
celebrate God for that word?
Now, I want you to pay attention. I've
started teaching already beyond the fact
that now I had to stop at verse seven
because all the way down there are
promises and prophecies.
They were promises, prophecies that had
gone ahead of us.
And we are in that time where we need to
start living the promises. when you
start leaving the prophecies.
If you read through verse two of Isaiah
chapter 60, he said something. He said,
"For behold, the darkness shall cover
the earth and gross darkness the
people." So God is not saying there
won't be darkness. All of these things
that we are experiencing in this time
and season, they have been written
before. The same way your life has been
designed beforehand, THE SAME WAY THIS
DARKNESS HAD BEEN PROPHESIED ahead of
time. But guess what? Bible say but the
Lord shall arise upon you and his glory
SHALL BE SEEN UPON YOU.
Meaning that THERE IS AN ASSIGNMENT UPON
YOU. The response to this darkness is
not complaining. The response TO THIS
PROBLEM IS NOT NAGGING BUT YOU ARE THAT
RESPONSE THAT WE'RE WAITING FOR. He said
FOR THE WORLD EARNESTLY awaits the
manifestation of the sons of God who are
the sons and daughters of God in this
house. SOMEBODY LET ME HEAR YOU SCREAM
GLORY.
THE WORLD IS WAITING FOR YOUR
MANIFESTATION.
>> You're not going to nag. Nagging will
not solve that problem. IT WON'T BRING
SOLUTION. But your evolution will bring
the solution we are looking for. Glory
with you Jesus. You know there are
certain things that have been prophesied
ahead. Confusion was prophesied. Moral
decline was prophesied.
Identity crisis was prophesied. But you
are the response to that thing.
>> Oh, somebody say I am the response. Oh,
you're not saying like you mean I'm the
response.
>> You are that response we are waiting
for. Glory to Jesus. Now I wrote I said
in all of this God has given a response
and like I said you are that response.
Retreat will not solve it. Can I say it
again? Can can I be sincere with us? Now
I'm not saying retreat is not good. But
if you like spend 24 hours ON THE
MOUNTAIN PRAYER WITHOUT ACTION IS
NOTHING.
>> Retreat will NOT STOP THIS DARKNESS.
RELIGIOUS activities will not do it.
But you rising up,
there is an instruction. Arise and
shine. Somebody say, "I will arise."
>> I arise.
>> Say, "I arise."
>> You're not saying, "I arise."
>> I arise.
>> You know, one of the things I need you
to understand is your arising is pivotal
to spreading light in the generation we
find ourselves.
You know, there are so many promises in
that scripture. Oh, kings will do this.
Men will bring this kings will come to
the brightness of your rising. Gentiles
will do this. They will do that. But
guess what? The world, the darkness does
not respond to potential. Can I talk to
somebody? Darkness does not respond to
potential. Kings don't bring their good
ties into potential.
>> They bring it to manifested solution.
>> I have an idea is not the end. The
product has to be solving something.
Excuse me, sir. You are a finished
product, but unfortunately you've
remained in the carton.
A finished product sitting in the
cartoon is of no use. Am I talking to
somebody?
>> You got a boutique blender, but you're
not blending anything. But guess what?
The the the the the capacity you have on
your inside is beyond bouti. I'm not
giving you free advertise. Bible says
greater he said he said oh you he said
greater is he that is in you than he
that is in the world. NOW THE GREATER ON
YOUR INSIDE IS NOT JUST SITTING THERE AS
DECORATION. I'm I'm PRESS SOMETHING. THE
GREATER ON YOUR INSIDE IS NOT JUST THERE
TO JUST IS NOT JUST FOR YOU TO BE
QUOTING the scripture. Is for you TO
STEP INTO BOARDROOMS. THEY HAVE BEEN
THERE FOR HOURS, 2 HOURS, 3 HOURS TRYING
TO FIND AN ANSWER and you enter and say
how about we tweak it this way and at
the speed of a minute the answer was
there.
Seeest thou a man diligent in his what?
>> Ah can we read it together? Proverbs
22:29. Can you give us that scripture so
we can read? He said, "Seeest thou a man
diligent in his works." Said, "He will
sit or stand before kings and not who?"
And not mere men. Now, it's not just a
scripture for you to confess. In fact,
if you lack excellence, you should not
quote that scripture.
If you do not understand why you are
here, that scripture does not belong to
you.
If you don't have a ready profile
solution to the darkness you are going
through right now, that scripture is not
for you. says, "Seeest thou a man." Can
we read it together? Everybody want to
go?
>> Read it louder.
>> Uhhuh.
>> The reason you are still standing with
unknown men is because you are not
diligent.
God when God I don't be stick you are
still a sticker until you are carved by
the car himself.
Can I can I be frank with us? Until the
author himself reveals the script to
you, you're still joking.
I got drive you. If you drive dele
without a prof without profounding
solution to a problem, you're a thief.
Am I saying you should not drive? No. If
you know me, I love cars.
But what are you doing? You know, I was
about doing a recording few days ago
about all these celebrated olos that we
have all around.
Once you have one iPhone 17 or iPhone
13, set up a ring light and you see that
and start doing all sort of rubbish. It
is because you lack the identity of who
you are. That's why you're following the
trend.
I don't have too much of time. I want
you to write this down. Kings do not
come to potential, they come to
manifested solution.
Write it down. Kings do not come to
potential. They come to manifested
solutions.
Kings are attracted by value. What value
are you bringing to the table?
It is and permit me to say this thing.
It is stupidity or it is stupidity for
them to be asking what do you bring to
the table and you're responding you are
the table.
>> Are you kidding me right now? So you are
the table that kings are deciding upon.
>> YOU ARE NOT THE TABLE. YOU ARE THE
SOLUTIONS THEY ARE BRINGING TO THE
TABLE. Somebody
>> don't NONSENSE WHEN STOP ASKING ME WHAT
I AM THE TABLE. Then the table will be
discussed on.
We will sit and put our hands on you and
discuss matters. Haven't you realized
that tables in the boardroom are remain
in the boardroom? They only hear of the
solutions. They only hear of ideas but
they don't enter the market space.
Say I am not the table. Say it. No, I am
not the table.
>> Kings are attracted by solutions. They
attracted by competence.
They are attracted by excellence.
You're a fashion designer. All you have
know how to s this why is when are you
going to crow
and you are praying kings will come.
They will not come.
Somebody say why you c I'm not cussing
you. Do you think all the kings want
have you seen kings apparel?
Amen. Somebody have you seen kings
apparel
and you're expecting kings to come to
the brightest of your eyes as how
you're an exile. All you know how to do
is is to go back.
You can't do bantto twist.
Don't be surprised. I mean I make care
so I know what I'm talking about.
You need to you ought to come up higher.
If you read the book of Revelation, at
least be with the first six, seven
chapters, God kept telling John, come up
higher because there are certain things
I cannot show you at the level you are.
There are certain solutions you can
never profile the level you are. THE
KIND OF RELATIONSHIPS, THE KIND OF
FRIENDS THAT YOU KEEP AT THAT LEVEL, GOD
CANNOT BRING ANY SOLUTION to you there.
Answer, but you know Jesus even starts
with sinner. Are you Jesus?
And who thought he was just sinners that
Jesus had with?
Haven't you realized the kind of people
that roam around Jesus?
Luke chapter 8, Bible spoke about
Susanna, the wife of somebody that
serves
what's that guy's name
or whatever.
Give me that scripture. Luke chapter 8,
I think there about you will see Joanna.
They mention names of men, noble men. Do
you think Jesus was just kashing?
I'm not against praying. If you know me,
I pray a lot. But what is the end result
of your prayer?
You have spent 10 hours cap to learnap.
God bless you. What is what has God
said? I I just You felt what? It's just
your emotions rising. We are a
generation that the world is waiting for
our response.
YOUR WORD SHOULD NOT BE AN ECHO. YOUR
WORD SHOULD NOT BE A NOISE. YOUR WORD
SHOULD BE a voice.
and trusting God that by the grace of
God in this place today you will
discover that thing that God has written
about you and not only will you discover
for some of you discovering is not the
problem but you have remained a mediocre
you have remained there
write this down the marketplace only
rewards manifestations
The marketplace only rewards what?
Manifestations.
Oh, sir, I have an idea. So, what's
next? You know, I I've written it. I've
done the So, what's next? Haven't you
realized that those that wins grants,
they don't just win grants by
documentation.
There's a real world problem they are
solving. And that's why the grant comes
to them. Haven't you realized with how
good you are to you in making shoes,
none of those top guys has responded and
say can can I can I
let's check scripture in the few minutes
that I have. Let's look at some of these
institutions that you know kings truly
came to the brightness of the horizon.
Daniel was the first person because of
time I would have lost love us to go
through all the scriptures. Daniel was
not just there because you know Daniel
gave Bible says Daniel knew by books.
Daniel served kings not one.
A particular king Darius he came to the
throne had this confusion. The mother
said there is a Daniel whose spirit of
excellence is found in him. CAN THE SAME
BE SAID ABOUT YOU? Is a spirit of
excellence found in you.
Can we pray in tong for a few for for
the next few minutes few seconds right
now? EVERYBODY EVERYONE PLEASE. SO
PRAYING IN TONGUES actually bruise
something on your inside. Kings word
youth, can you see where you are? Where
you seated? Can you rewind the spirit
for just a few moment right now?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Stop looking
at me. Stop staring at me. I want you TO
ACTUALLY PRAY BECAUSE THERE IS A
SOLUTION ON YOUR INSIDE THAT THE WORLD
IS WAITING FOR. BUT IT CAN ONLY COME
OUT. IT CAN'T JUST BE SITTING DOWN THERE
DOING NOTHING. CAN YOU ACTUALLY PRAY?
Can you pray? Can you pray?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Hallelujah.
You know, talking about these men, this
institution, I'm going to talk about
Daniel, Joseph, and Esther. There are so
many of them in the Bible, Nehemiah. But
these men, they were not just after
escaping poverty.
That is somebody's mindset AND THAT'S
WHY YOU ARE still poor.
IF YOUR PLAN IS JUST TO ESCAPE POVERTY,
I bring you good news that you might
still remain there.
The plan is not to escape poverty. Sir,
the plan is to bring influence.
The plan is to represent the kingdom
well.
When you represent the kingdom well,
when you bring influence to the table,
automat poverty and influence are not
friends.
They are not.
Daniel influenced an entire kingdom. Not
only Daniel, talk about the three Hebrew
boys
because they represented God well in
their space. They knew what they would.
They know this is what I am cut out for.
And they stayed in their lane. Not only
did they stay in that lane, they
represented the kingdom well. How well
are you representing the kingdom in your
space?
Can I look at you as an accountant in
your space and I can say of a truth you
are a son of God or you have cut books
back and forth?
How well can you stand present?
How well are you still GOING TO LIFT UP
ONLY HANDS WHEN THE RESULT IS NOT
SHOWING FORTH?
Talk about Esther.
Esther didn't just sit on that throne
for the ground. No, she sat on that
throne to save a nation, TO SAVE A
PEOPLE. IMAGINE ESTHER WAS NOT ON THAT
THRONE. They would have taken off an
entire nation, an entire generation.
Is our uncle said, "I hope you know that
you are seated on that throne room for
such A TIME AS THIS. CAN THE SAME BE SET
UP ABOUT YOU, THAT YOU ARE SITTING IN
THAT OFFICE FOR SUCH A TIME AS THIS?"
Can we say the same about you THAT YOU
ARE A FASHION DESIGNER IN YOUR SPACE SO
THAT YOU CAN START SEWING FOR FOR PEOPLE
IN GOVERNANCE SO THAT YOU CAN START
BRINGING kingdom principles kingdom
manifestations INTO PLACE INTO POLITICS
INTO governance but no all you are
thinking about is how to pay the next
debt. You should pay your debt to but
beyond the debt beyond your daily bread
beyond your daily 2k. Hello. Why will
you be confessing daily 2K?
Well, maybe it's Daily 2K dolls.
>> Somebody didn't catch that.
How is it going to come up higher in
your thinking?
>> Stepping out. Stepping out for the for
my 2K. Are you kidding me?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO INFLUENCE ANYTHING
with 2,000 NRA. NOBODY'S GOING TO
SITTING DOWN IN THIS AUDITORIUM. It cost
millions.
I was listening to pastor I mean I was
discussing with with our ministers in
the in the in the green room you know
pastor Okoda I was listening to him few
days ago and I was talking about how he
met a guy on a plane going to the US
said the guy was telling him that he can
command 10,000 people he has he has a
community of 10,000 people that he can
put a call through to them right now and
tell them to do one two three and they
will do it like he said he was like oh
yeah let's put it to this pastor was
like in 5 minutes the guy set up a
meeting an impromptu Excuse me, sir.
When you set up a meeting and people are
not responsive, you don't have influence
in their lives.
When you're trying to pull a string and
it's not pulling, check your values.
It's not pride though. After this
meeting, there are some relationships
you should let go. And there are certain
relationship you run after.
He said was like in 5 minutes this guy
set up a meeting. over 10,000 people
appeared virtual meeting and he said he
gave an instruction okay guys you know I
know it's an from two and I want you to
do this this this pap said in in in that
space of five minute 4,000 people had
responded sir it is influence
unfortunately I doubt is in the is in
the Christian space
what are we influencing believers kings
world youth what are we influencing
are we together how well are we
representing the kingdom But it all
boils down to knowing who you are.
Because if you don't know what you are
cut out for, you will not represent
well.
IF YOU HAVE NOT FOUND PURPOSE, WHY AM I
HERE? WHAT WAS WRITTEN ABOUT ME?
You will not represent well. You will
just be thinking about you, you and you.
Oh, you want to get the latest iPhone
17? News flash 18 is on the way.
Haven't
you realized that they messed some of
you up? They not in this auditori.
But they mess some people up because of
iPhone 13. 18 is on the way.
Some of you because of Shama.
Should I go on? Are you sure? Write this
down. See your rising as your
responsibility.
See your rising, you're becoming your
you're bringing influence. See it as
your responsibility. It is your
responsibility to actually rise up to
the task. It is your responsibility to
discover that which was written about
you. It is your responsibility to begin
to bring impact influence to the
kingdom.
Darkness will rise darkness the people
said but the Lord he will not. He has
risen upon you. The question is will you
bright the light? Will you shine the
light? We don't need your light in THE
CHURCH. GOD'S PLAN IS NOT TO RAISE TOUCH
STARS. GOD'S PLAN IS NOT TO RAISE TOUCH
CELEBRITIES. NO.
Of what use is your iPhone or your Nokia
or whatever phone you're holding? Of
what use is the touch light in this
place?
It has no value. But when you enter a
dark place, flip it on. Everywhere is
brightened up. They need your light
somewhere, sir.
Rise up on your feet, somebody. They
need your light somewhere.
They need your light somewhere.
You know the problem we have in our
generation is a lot of people want the
table of kings but nobody wants to be
disciplined to get to that table.
It is not possible that you want a
king's table and you will not be
disciplined to get there.
Do you know what it takes to be a king?
Do you not know what it takes to stand
before those kings?
Sitting with kings is not a joke.
If you must sit at the king's table as
you're standing because you're about to
pray, let me know how many minutes I
have left. I want you to pick your pen
and your paper because I want you to
write these things down. If you must
bring influence, if you must sit with
the kings,
there are five things that you must
bring to the table. Remember, you're not
the table, but there are five things
that you must bring to the table to be
able to sit with kings. Number one, you
must bring excellence to mediocrity.
you is not a maybe it's a must.
There are level of mediocrities
everywhere and the and that's why Bible
says the the word endlessly wait your
manifestation. The waiting is your
bringing the excellence to mediocrity.
Number two thing that you must bring you
must bring wisdom to confusion.
You must bring what? Wisdom to
confusion. Men are confused. They don't
know what to do. They think they do but
they don't.
You will see a grown man, you will think
he knows his right from his left. He
doesn't. He needs an answer.
He needs an answer. But you are that
answer. Number three thing you must
bring to sit with me. You must bring
integrity to responsibility.
No matter how he's doing you to take
that money. Excuse me, sir. Stay calm.
Money will finish now. Human being
remain.
No matter the amount of money, it will
finish.
But how well can you stand and say while
I was handling that duty, my integrity
can be put to test and I will not fail.
How many if I give you three number four
you must bring solution to impossible
problems.
Can you see I didn't say problems. There
are problems that we already know that
there are problems and they can be
solved. But there are impossible
problems.
And number five, you must bring hope to
darkness.
You must bring what? Hope to darkness.
SO WHEN YOU APPEAR BEFORE MEN, WHAT THEY
SEE IS solution of the day.
WHAT THEY SEE IS LIGHT HAS COME.
OH,
my light has come.
Oh,
My light has come.
kings, what you've touched, my light HAS
COME. HAS YOUR LIGHT COME? OH.
MY [screaming]
[singing]
>> is your light here.
[music]
[singing]
>> As I round off this morning, we can talk
about a lot of men in the scripture.
Daniel, Joseph, Esther, Nehemiah.
But there's one common factor to all of
them. God.
>> In the beginning, God. In the end,
if you will discover what was written
about you, if you will bring influence
to the table, if you will represent the
kingdom well, you and God, you have to
take the same step. God can, you can't
afford God taking five steps ahead of
you. And I and I I know what I'm talking
about. As he takes one step, you take it
together.
I mean, IS IT NOT GREATER IS HE THAT IS
IN YOU? SO WHEN THE GREATER IS TAKING
TWO STEPS, HOW MANY STEPS are you
taking? You are taking the two with him.
WE MOVE TOGETHER. SAID, FOR I AM SEATED
WITH CHRIST.
>> You are a kingdom envoy.
I've come in the volume of the book. It
was written about me to do your will, oh
God.
I've come in the volume of the book. It
was written about me. Get a neighbor to
do your will, oh Lord. Are you going to
do his will? I will do your will. Do
your will.
Do your will. [music]
>> It begins with responding. Say, Lord,
what will you have me do?
THAT'S WHERE IT ALL BEGINS FROM. IT IS
IN RESPONDING TO WHAT WE GOD HAVE YOU DO
THAT BEGINS TO PRODUCE THAT INFLUENCE
THAT BEGINS to produce THAT
RESPONSIBILITY THAT HELPS YOU TO FLY
HIGH ABOVE YOUR COLLEAGUES. Somebody
still waiting for me to leave prayer
point. If your neighbor cannot pray,
maybe you should think nebo because let
me tell you something. I TRUST GOD SO
WELL THAT in this IN THE YOUTH CHURCH OF
KING THE TIME TO START SENDING ENVOYS TO
THE MARKETPLACE IS NOW. THAT TIME IS
NOW. THE TIME FOR US TO BE WELL
REPRESENTED IN POLITICS, IN GOVERNANCE,
IN ENTERTAINMENT INDUSTRY, IN SPACES.
THAT TIME IS NOW. THAT TIME IS NOW. IS
SOMEBODY STILL WAITING? ARE YOU PRAYING?
Are you praying? I said get a neighbor.
GET A NEIGHBOR AND HELP YOUR BROTHER.
HELP YOUR SISTER.
Your will be done.
JUST KEEP PRAYING. KEEP PRAYING. AND ON
THE earth using me.
Your will be done
in the moon
and on the earth
using me. GOD IS COUNTING ON YOU SIR.
GOD IS COUNTING ON YOU MAN. JESUS
LEADING PRAYER HE SAID THY KINGDOM COME
THY WILL BE done on earth as it is in
heaven. If the will of God is going to
be done on the earth the way it is in
the heaven, he's going to use you. He's
going to use you. IS SOMEBODY WILLING?
IS SOMEBODY READY?
Somebody pray. Somebody pray. This table
is too cold for me.
They are waiting FOR YOUR MANIFESTATION.
BE WAITING. THEY'RE WAITING. THEY'RE
WAITING FOR YOUR MANIFESTATION.
Can you give me a 2 minutes timer?
What will you have ME DO? WHAT WILL YOU
HAVE ME DO? What will you have me do?
What will you have me do? SOMEBODY KEEP
PRAYING. KEEP PRAYING. THAT IS WHY YOU
ARE HERE. THAT IS WHY YOU ARE HERE. WHAT
IS THAT WHICH WAS WRITTEN ABOUT ME?
>> [screaming]
>> Change neighbor. Change neighbor. Change
neighbor. I'm trusting God. And in this
place, YOU THOUGHT THE TIME THE TIME FOR
US TO BEGIN to occupy spaces. We have to
be well represented. Remember, we are
kings. We have no taste FOR ME RELIGION.
WITHOUT CHANGE.
YOU ARE A CHANGE AGENT. ENOUGH OF JUST
COMING TO CHURCH AND JUST SITTING DOWN
THERE AND ALL YOU'RE JUST DOING IS JUST
TO do Sunday sun Sunday meeting. The
time to walk into the market space. The
time to walk into politics. The time to
walk into entertainment and start
shining YOUR LIGHT. YOU ARE THE LIGHT.
YOU ARE THAT LIGHT. YOU ARE THAT LIGHT.
IF [music] YOUR NEIGHBOR is not praying,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD CHANGE YOUR NEIGHBOR.
The glory of the youth is IN THEIR
STRENGTH.
THE GLORY OF THE YOUTH IS IN THEIR
KINGS YOUTH THOUGHTS. THE TIME IS NOW.
THE REVIVAL that was promised our
fathers. THE TIME IS NOW. THE TIME IS
NOW. THE TIME IS NOW. REVIVAL IS NOT
JUST US COMING TOGETHER PRAYING. REVIVAL
IS WHEN WE START ENTERING THOSE SPACES
AND FLIPPING THE SCRIPT.
IF SOMEBODY PRAY, LET ME GIVE YOU 30
MORE SECONDS.
Leave your TABLE AND FIND ANOTHER
NEIGHBOR. LEAVE YOUR TABLE AND FIND
ANOTHER NEIGHBOR. KING YOUTH CHURCH, THE
TIME IS NOW. THE VISION, THE REVELATION,
THE REVIVAL THAT WAS SHOWN, THAT WAS
GIVEN, THE mandate that WAS GIVEN TO OUR
FATHER.
We are that generation.
bringing it to full manifestation AND IT
WILL ONLY HAPPEN
WHEN YOU FIND GOD ASKING HIM WHAT WILL
YOU HAVE ME DO
CAME TO WHAT YOU THOUGHT WILL YOU STIR
UP YOUR SPIRIT
STIR UP YOUR SPIRIT STIR UP YOUR SPIRIT
STIR UP YOUR SPIRIT stir up YOUR SPIRIT
you are NOT JUST THAT COMPANY'S MANAGER
BECAUSE OF THE SALARY. NO,
God has PLACED YOU THERE FOR A REASON.
GOD HAS PLACED YOU THERE FOR A REASON.
You are not just an entertainer because
you KNOW HOW TO PLAY COMEDY. NO,
YOU HAVE BEEN SENT THERE TO TURN ON THE
LIGHT. SOMEBODY TURN ON THE LIGHT.
KINGS, WHAT YOU THOUGHT? TURN ON THE
LIGHT. TURN ON THE LIGHT. TURN ON THE
LIGHT. TURN ON THE FLAME. FOUND THE
FLAME. I'm going to give you an
opportunity to find two more neighbor.
MOVE TO THE NEXT NEIGHBOR AND HELP YOUR
NEIGHBOR PRAY.
THE TIME IS NOW. THE TIME IS NOW. THE
TIME IS NOW.
THE SUPERNATURAL MANDATE,
THE SUPERNATURAL MANDATE WILL BEGIN TO
FIND EXPRESSION IN THE BOARDROOMS, IN
THE ENTERTAINMENT SPACE, in politics.
WHERE ARE THE DANIELS OF MY GENERATION?
WHERE ARE THE ESTERS? WHERE ARE THE
DEBORAS? WHERE ARE THE JOSEPHS? WHERE IS
THAT DAVID?
RAISE YOUR VOICE. THERE ARE HUNDREDS OF
US IN THIS PLACE. RAISE YOUR VOICE.
RAISE YOUR VOICE.
FIND YOUR LAST NEIGHBOR RIGHT NOW AND
HOLD THE TWO HAND OF YOUR NEIGHBOR AND
ALIGN WITH THE HOLY SPIRIT. AND ALIGN
WITH THE HOLY SPIRIT.
ZERO TASTE. ZERO TASTE FOR ME RELIGION
WITHOUT CHANGE. THAT IS WHO WE ARE. THAT
IS WHO WE ARE. THE TIME TO BRING THAT
CHANGE IS NOW.
YES. THE TIME TO FAVOR ZION HAS COME.
BUT favor does not respond to
mediocrity. FAVOR RESPOND TO POWER.
FAVOR RESPOND TO EXCELLENCE. Favor
respond to competence.
Lord, reveal to me. Reveal to me.
Reveal to me.
[screaming]
[music]
>> [music]
>> It will carry you, but it will carry you
when you have been able to find you. You
can only find you with God.
>> [music]
>> Somebody pray.
Kings youth church, the time to spread
the light is now. THE TIME TO SPREAD THE
LIGHT IS NOW.
Somebody find God. Find God.
Find the God of
lift up your hands everyone
just one passion
one purpose
just to know you more and more
that's where it begins from when I know
you I'll find that competence is in you
sir you just need to find God just one
passion
my brother on pause.
>> Can I hear you right now?
[singing]
[music]
>> WHEN YOU KNOW GOD, WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN? YEAH.
>> Is there a life without God? Can I hear
you say right now? No. [singing]
>> Can we sing it like we know it?
No.
>> Let me know you, Lord.
Let me know.
[singing and music]
>> When I know you
>> when I know you are
>> I want you to actually lift up your
hands and sing that song. It's you and
God right now in just one
>> without the choir. Let me hear you
somebody.
>> Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
>> Projection. Help us with help us with
lyrics. When I know you, I will find me.
Can we sing it three more times? In just
one passion, Lord.
>> One purpose.
Hey,
when I know you, Lord, when I know you,
Lord,
one more time. Just one [music] person,
Lord.
Just one
[singing]
>> all these things are simple.
>> I tell you, hey,
>> to know [singing]
you more [music] and more.
>> When I know you, Lord,
>> when I know you, I'll find.
[music and singing]
>> No life, no life.
>> Come on. Come on. Be life. No life. No
life.
[singing and music]
>> Let me know you. Let me know you, Lord.
>> Let me know [singing] you.
>> When I know [music] you, Lord,
I know you are. [music]
>> Somebody straight forth, wherever you
are. I know I've I've shot my time, but
straight for the hand where you are.
I'm going to give you 30 seconds. Close
your eyes, everyone. 30 seconds. And I'm
being sincere here. See, above all else,
God.
That's that's that influence we're
talking about, that kingdom
representation we're talking about, it
all begins with God.
Just one word from God can flip the
script.
One instruction can change the entire
story line. I'm going to give you 30
seconds and I'm sure it's not more than
30 seconds. So if you like play don't
play. You are going to pray in the Holy
Ghost loud, fervent, and clear. Please
no music so that you you won't be
writing on music and be thinking you're
praying. 30 seconds at a count of three.
Please give me time so I can run this
session off. At a count of three, 30
seconds you are praying in tongues
aligning with the Holy Spirit. King's
word. That is what we do here, right?
That's our culture. Are you ready? At a
count of three, I want you to bust out
loud, fervent, and clear. One, two,
three. Can I hear you pray? Somebody
right now. Everybody. Everybody, you
have 30 seconds. Can I have that timer?
Can I have that timer, please? Come on.
Come on. What you are doing is you are
exploring and you're finding your way to
God.
He that prayth in an unknown tongue,
speaketh not unto man.
Albeit,
>> he speaketh unto God. How be it speaketh
misery?
>> He that speaketh in an unknown tongue
edifyth himself.
Brethren, building up your most holy
faith, praying in the Holy Ghost,
you have 20 more seconds.
Somebody,
I want you to stay on that spot. Stay on
that one spot and strike forth your hand
and pray in the spirit. STAY ON THAT
SPOT YOU ARE. THAT SPOT YOU ARE AND
STRIKE FORTH YOUR HAND. Reach out to
God.
Reach out. Reach out.
>> Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
>> Leaving this conference, the Pioneers
Conference 2026. You are stepping into
your space. Pioneering great and mighty
things. Pioneering solutions.
Pioneering solutions.
I kid you not. IN THE LAST ONE MONTH,
God has given me four solutions. Four. I
AM WORKING ON TWO as I speak to you. ONE
IS IN THE TECH SPACE. ONE IS IN THE
PRODUCTION of foods.
WATCH OUT FOR YOU.
I'M SERIOUS. WATCH OUT FOR ME.
Because of somebody that is not praying,
I will give you 15 SECONDS EXTRA.
SOMEBODY FIND GOD. THIS IS NOT a gimmick
right now. We are not doing church here.
The real deal. The real deal is in God.
>> SUPERNATURAL ARMY RISE. OH,
>> you are king's WORLD. OH, YOU HAVE NO
TASTE FOR ME RELIGION WITHOUT CHANGE.
THAT CHANGE YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT IS A
SOLUTION that you bring to the table.
AND THAT SOLUTION CAN ONLY COME WHEN YOU
HAVE FOUND YOU. AND YOU CAN ONLY FIND
YOU WHEN YOU HAVE FIND GOD.
SO CAN YOU PRESS into that FLOW
solutions
alighty
Almighty God,
>> what will your generation do?
>> Our generation
[singing]
shall praise [music]
your name.
>> Our generation
[singing]
shall praise [music]
your
name. Our generation,
>> our generation
[singing]
shall praise [music]
your name.
Our generation
[singing]
shall praise
your
name. [music]
>> Somebody celebrate the Holy Ghost in his
house right now.
Somebody celebrate the Holy Ghost.
CAME TO ALL THE YOUTH CHURCH. CELEBRATE
THE HOLY GHOST.
>> I didn't feel like stopping.
>> First it was fragrance
>> and it turned to fire.
>> What's your what's your worship?
>> Is how you're going to respond. This is
how I win my battle. Earth. [music] It
was fragrant. [singing]
>> Was
it
[music] to fire
is my
>> worship is our
[music]
battle.
>> Holy Spirit.
>> That's how you're going to win your
battle.
>> [music]
>> Somebody speak
[music]
TO
>> [music]
>> HEY EVERYBODY.
[music]
This is our
This is [music] our way. [singing]
This is our way. Hey, this by worship.
[music]
Hallelujah.
>> Somebody celebrate Jesus.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Somebody should help me cuz what is
going on here?
Someone what is going on here?
Something is [music] happening.
[screaming]
Fire.
>> [music]
>> See if they're looking in that place.
>> Something is happening right now.
Something is happening right now.
Don't miss on your way.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
>> I am.
[music]
Someone is scream.
Somebody is
kings. What you do? Supernatural
[screaming] help me. Somebody
is happening right here. Something's
moving. Something's changing. [music]
>> Seems
like
something
[music]
chang
[music] something
>> Oh. Oh,
[music]
hallelujah.
>> Heaven on earth.
>> Somebody say, "I'm heaven on earth."
>> Ah, you're too cold on this side.
>> Say, "I'm heaven on earth."
>> I'm on earth.
You know something just dawned on me
right here when the Lord said, you know,
Bible says in the beginning the earth
was without form and void. And it dawned
on me that even in this generation the
earth is without form and void. But
guess what? When God said, "Let there be
light," I appeared.
>> When God said, "Let there be light. I
shot forth. Oh,
oh, [screaming] I forth. I am the
light." Ah, somebody is still waiting
while I speak my own. I am the light
that the world has been waiting for.
[music] I am the light. I am that
solution. I am that manif.
I am that light. I am that solution.
I have been transported from darkness
into the marvelous light. So I now
become the light.
I become the light.
When darkness are done.
[screaming]
[music]
>> Now listen, they're going to change it.
You say, "Where's darkness [music] at
the [singing] sight of light?"
>> Listen carefully. Yeah. Hear this.
Where's darkness at the sight of me?
[music]
Me
>> evaporated at the gl of me. Hey,
>> I am the light
shine bright.
>> When they look
>> now listen
as they look my face they become the
light.
Listen, I know somebody is still not
catching the revelation. Let me show
you. Greater is he that is in who?
Listen. Greater is he that is where?
>> Than he that is what? Pay attention now.
He that is in me is what? Is light.
Automatically what am I?
>> So where's darkness at the sight of me?
>> Are you kidding me? Heavenated at the gl
[music] of me.
>> Now listen, I am the light that makes
their face shine [music] bright
>> so bright. And as they look my face,
they become [music]
[music]
Immol.
>> All the light in this house. Can you
scream? [screaming]
[music]
>> Look at your neighbor. Say hello light.
Say hello light.
>> Hello light.
>> There's an anointing in this place.
There's an anointing here. Don't worry,
we're still coming back.
Okay.
Say hello light as you have your seat in
God's presence.
>> Come on. Come on. Let's do that. Yellow
light.
Can we celebrate God in this place?
God is here.
God is here and I know it.
>> God is here and I know it.
Pastor T, I think you should leave that
drums because the more you are seated on
that drums,
>> I think all our lineups are here. Right.
Okay. We're about to enter another zone.
See, let me help you. Those guys on that
chair, you're not helping yourself. Hey,
see those guys?
Are you Tik Tok guys?
Then let me help you. This next session
is beyond fireside chat. In fact, I love
that word fireside chat.
See, as you're talking, please be with
your pain and your daughter. I wish it's
journal, whatever you want to call it.
And as you're talking,
if I were you, I'll be praying under my
breath.
Because you will hear some truth that
can flip your account overnight.
I'm not joking.
The time for us to find that relevance
is now.
Don't let anybody lie to you. Church,
we've met they've I won't say we cuz I'm
not part of them. They've made that
mistakes over the years. We are the one
that are changing it. Church, we need
money. We need fame. And we need
influence.
Can we say it again? We need what?
>> Please say it. We need what?
>> Let me help you arrange it. You need
money. You need fame. You need
influence. Can we say our what? Money.
>> Don't let anybody want you.
Some people go whine but no panic. Your
God is not a mediocre God.
If I don't step down from this place.
[laughter]
Is somebody ready? Please welcome my
beautiful wife.
He's my wife. Oh, come on. Come on. Come
on.
Can you I won't leave this place. Can
you celebrate my wife?
>> [cheering]
>> Are you married? Receive your wife.
>> If you want your spouse, celebrate my
wife.
>> Hallelujah.
>> At least pastor to me can relate.
Um before I step down, hand over to Mike
to her. Please let me welcome um our
fathers and our mothers. I mean, of
course.
She doesn't like me calling this, but
we'll call her. Pastor Jimmy Parker. I
see you.
Pastor Golangh
we is men of God we are calling oh
the highly esteemed deacon
baby
thank you so much for joining us
over to you darling wife
>> yes sir
>> hallelujah
>> kings world youth hallelujah
>> come on that was a powerful session were
you blessed
>> were you blessed like this is actually a
question Right. Hallelujah. Praise God.
Um it's good to have you here. It's good
to see everyone from different
installations. It brings back memories,
right? Um praise God
history. Um and you're a part of it. You
are part of the history that you know is
going down today. And right now we are
moving into the um one of the powerful
sessions in today's conference and
that's the combined fireside chat. Um so
we have people in the ministry
We have people in businesses and in
career and guess what they are king's
word.
Every one of them are kings world. They
are our fathers, our mothers, our
pastors, our leaders. They are um in in
the leadership and they will be blessing
us today. And um all we just need you to
do is to connect. Right. Listen as PM
has said um write down some things cuz
some great things will be discussed here
today. Okay. Um Amen. So I will be
calling their names and as they come up
um they will just take the seat and
we'll start off. Okay. I'm starting with
pastor Timmy
Omisha resident pastor Kings word
[cheering] miss
be managing partners I shall be park
pastor Olu fire resident pastor kings
aete pastor Victor Balogu associate
pastor Kingsu
dickinad
manager ESG and impact reporting in MTN
Nigeria, Pastor Tamita Yayu, Associate
Pastor Kingswood VI, and our very own
Pastor Daw,
managing director, Cadra Assets.
Hallelujah.
Okay, so protocol, we're supposed to
tell you about the arrangement. So,
pardon me if I'm going to move you
around. So, please come. Yes, ma'am.
Pastor Deli, you here. Dickin next. And
Pastor Gali, thank you. Yeah, you are in
the spirit. [laughter]
Okay, everyone. So, we are going
straight into the conversation. I've
mentioned their names and I've also um
in a way mention um where they are from,
but in the course of the conversation,
you'll be hearing more. So, pastors, you
are welcome. Thank you very much, sir
and ma for yielding um to this. Please,
can we have the microphones? There's no
microphone with them.
Okay. So in the meantime, I guess I have
to pass this around. All right. So we
are starting off um with pastor pastor
Timay and pastors Tumi. Um the question
I have here is when did you first know
that God had written something specific
for your life? Not a general blessing,
not just every general thing, but a
specific assignment saying that you are
pastors. Of course you have your
businesses and career. But when did you
know that um this specific thing for my
life you know God has written it? Uh
while we wait. Okay.
Thank you
Pastor T. You can go first. [laughter]
for me when I started you know
experiencing that change in my life
specifically was in 2012 I was I was a
student um and then I for I think it was
particular Sunday somebody invited me to
a king's word church in Jabod and for
the first time I was hearing things like
you're not a mistake you know there's a
purpose for your life you are more than
this you know there is much more to you
than this physical person I'm seeing
here And at that time permit me to say
in local paral something called anywhere
ble face and I was that kind [laughter]
of person I didn't have anything I just
wanted to you know I you know if you get
what I'm saying you know what I'm saying
you are not really you don't have any
goals you don't have any you know
nothing you're just moving anywhere the
you know wind pushes you and all that
you know so but in that service I heard
that God has a purpose for me and one of
the um um very strong scriptures that
was used that day was Jeremiah 15. But
you know before I was formed in my
mother's womb that God knows me and he
has ordained me. So that was the
beginning of the journey to discovering
you know who you know God has made me to
be. And one of the things I'd like to
say is that in that journey
what made it clearer was the fact that
was that fellowship with God. That was
the beginning of a launch into a journey
with God where you know there was so
much fellowship. I I couldn't I I I got
to a place where I couldn't detach
myself from that fellowship. I was so
drunk about it and then it was in that
precept upon precept that God began to
you know even by the um inward witness
you know to you know
>> began
>> you know that's it.
>> Thank you. That's a good place to clap.
>> Pastor Tumi.
>> Oh good afternoon everyone. So I I would
say that the first time
let's just start from where he stopped
or where he started because I for one I
I felt like cuz I the kind of church my
parents attended they had this
expression of um the supernatural is
some sort. So I kind of knew that I was
called or you know it was a CNR. So so I
understand that I was called but
something like that. So I I knew that
part of me
>> and when I was younger give prophecy
here say some things here and there but
it got redefined or clearer when I
joined Kingswood and I joined King's
word
>> October
2nd 2020 2011. So at that time I was I
think 15. So it was clear to me that um
it wasn't clear from this first Sunday
obviously I just love the atmosphere. I
just love the people. It was different
for where I was coming from. But it got
clearer when
>> I started making decisions. I could
remember vividly when I wanted to go to
because when I joined Kingswood was when
I wanted to um get an admission into the
uni. So I was still sharing with
someone. I was there. There was someone
that was working it out and all like
that. I wanted to go to Latech. Then um
I was the letter was to come out the
next day. Then somebody in church walked
up to me and said we used to call him
PD. He said young man how is it going? I
said I'm fine. He said have you prayed?
What what school are you going? I said
latte. I said have you prayed about it?
And I said ah and now we are going to la
now things like that. And next thing he
said was that pray with Jeremiah 15
taken off from where he stay. So he
prayed pray with Jeremiah 15. And for
the first time I prayed not in tongues.
I prayed with scripture. And as I was
praying, not necessar sounded like I
knew how to pray. I was praying the way
I knew it, but I was just repeating
scriptures. And the first time I saw a
train, like a train detour.
>> Wow.
>> Like he went off track and did a U-turn.
>> And next thing I heard was the second
day or the third day. The person that
was helping us work, he just called my
mom and said I my mind cannot allow me
to do it because what will happen is
that when this guy get to 300 level or
something the vis will have been out and
they will send him packing and that's
how I got to know Foo and right from
that time it was just a change of tra um
trajectory. I just my life thoughts
totally changed. I got
>> I got in the flow and like you said the
fellowship got better.
>> Hallelujah. Okay. Um did you all get the
scripture? They all said the two of them
said the scripture. What's the scripture
>> exactly? So take notes and go and pray
with that scripture. Praise God. So this
question is going to dein
pastor Dolan as well. Thank you.
All right. Um Deacin I know that you say
this often [laughter]
uh that oh I just want to serve the
tables. I know you say this often and at
the same time you are in the career
space and you are doing great and mighty
things there. Um so this question is um
for those carrying both a ministry title
and business and career assignment. When
did you realize your scroll had more
than one chapter is not just about the
table is alo about the career you know
you have to you're excelling in that
space you're excelling you know as as a
pastor as well. At what point did you
know have that realization that it's not
just one face?
>> Good afternoon everyone. Um
so the the work of the ministry doesn't
necessarily have to be the title of a
pastor.
>> Doesn't have to be the title of an
apostle or as the Bible said in first
Corinthians. Ironically that was a
scripture I was reading before coming
here. 1 Corinthians um 12 27 not 27
downwards. They are the pastors. So,
[laughter]
>> so well I think the work of the ministry
is being useful in your father's house.
That's as simple as it is.
>> And so while I had always wanted or
desired to be a career person, what I
have then found out is the same skill
set I can use in the workplace or in the
marketplace can also be used in the
church.
>> Amazing.
>> So that for me is real. It's not about
the title or whatever. It's about
whatever you tell me to do, I will do.
Wherever I see gap, I will do to the
best of my ability. Are there clashes?
Yes.
>> Are there times when one pull um the
other? Yes. So that's where you then
need wisdom on how to balance. So I
think I get I got to know that
practically living my life normally just
wanting to go to church or be part of a
church and not just want to sit down
>> and not do anything. 20 2015 when I came
back fully to Lagos um from the east and
I was here I think I tried I tried like
two three different units before I later
settled on but the major driving thing
was I just don't want to come to the
Sunday service and not and just sit and
not do anything so that is the way where
you'll be able to match what you really
want to do which is the marketplace
>> and match it with serving in and so my
My my what I would say is you don't
necessarily need to wait for the title
of a pastor, a deacon, a post. As long
as you are serving your father's house,
you are doing the work of the ministry.
>> Amazing. Pastor Dali,
>> same question.
>> Yes, please. Same question.
>> Okay, great.
Yeah, thanks for having me and I think
it's a powerful conference.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Um, so when do I when did I realize to
be honest, I'm not sure. Um
so for me I sort of grew up with pastors
at some point in my life. So the likes
of Dr. K, Pastor Noel,
Pastor Don, Pastor Lan, I grew up
together. I was staying with Pastor T.
Pastor T is my cousin and we're all in
the same house. But I wasn't always like
a serious Christian. I was sort of a bad
boy. But there was some point that God
arrested me and I think maybe all the
seeds have been planted at some point
just had fruion. So um back then in
school I was a pastor in school um um at
some point and I thought maybe all my
life I was going to be a pastor. Um cuz
the easy thing was I mean when you're
done with school you sort of you
transition into pastor. When I left
school I was thinking should I wait
behind? I was posted to a campus then I
think it was uh I can't really remember
but um fast forward um I was pastoring
um I was involved in the sales system as
well in in in church but I needed to get
a job um and when I was going to get a
job I think what I put on my CV was
really I pastored in school leadership
skill but I got a job I interned there
and I became um a staff I was converted
But like every was saying that a lot of
the things I did being at the workplace
were things I learned in church. I can
remember back then I'll bring some of my
colleagues together. We are praying for
for the office, praying for their
progress, praying that things turn
around. Um I was working in love. Um I
was sort of ensuring that my superiors,
my leaders, I was there for them. I was
diligent. Most times a lot of my
colleagues back then they're closed. I
work late hours. Um I self-studied.
So and there were a lot of things that I
sort of learned in church in how to
stand out, how to be diligent, um how to
use the word of God to get results,
faith and everything. And I found out I
began to excel in my career. I began to
get promotions that were that that my um
colleagues were not getting. And
sometime people come and ask why are you
doing all these things? And sometimes it
was an ability to really point them to
God. So I would say that there was um a
point where I realized that there was a
tool. I think was more was just being
diligent, being faithful with whatever
has been committed into my hands.
>> Wow. Wow. Praise God.
Um cuz this question is going to Pastor
Tqu
and um Pastor Victor. Okay. Um what did
being faithful in your assignment cost
you that nobody in this room? You are
right. You're in the spirit. I want her
to
>> I want her to go first. [laughter]
What did being faithful in your
assignment cost you that nobody in this
room would see on your highlights real?
Like it's not on Instagram. It's not
there. [laughter]
And pastor, before you answer that
question, so I've always wanted to ask
you this question. How how do you do it?
You live in Lagos.
You pastor Jabodi as how. So being
faithful in your assignment, what has it
cost you?
>> Okay, thank you everyone. Good
afternoon. Um I'm very happy to be here.
Thank you for having me. What has it
cost me? We don't have all the time
because I have stories for days.
[laughter]
I have stories for days, but I think I
would just stay with maybe something
that is coming to mind now, which is um
I was okay with people not
understanding.
So it cost me that um
I wasn't trying to get everybody on
board because there were a lot of
everybody has an opinion about what you
should do. And the funny thing with my
life is that or the funny thing with the
things I'm doing is that the people in
church or Christians have their opinion.
The people outside church also have
their opinion. So somebody outside
church would say why are you in Lagos
and pastoring in Jabu your business how
are you doing there was a time that I
had a 9 to5 and I was working in a
consulting yes
>> and it was as in you are not are you
okay even people in my office I try not
to say because I really don't want talk
talk but sometimes when they get to find
out because I'm also not trying to hide
they will be like what is going on so
you leave here on Friday sometimes we
work um what do they call this thing
where you walk sometimes and hybrid you
work um remotely sometimes but it was
just a lot and those ones will have
their opinion but you think when you get
to church or the people that are
Christians they still have an issue like
you cannot be outside and pastoring you
are not serious with your you you stay
with your sheep the pastors will live
with your sheep you are not doing it how
can you as in they don't get it and they
don't get it from a place of you are
trying they don't get it from they they
talking from a place of you never ready
>> like you are not serious. So the people
in church or somewhere that a Christian
or somebody that's even a pastor would
see you and say you're living in
the Lord is your strength and then
somebody outside is also saying what are
you doing
>> and it was just a lot of
>> opinions were clashing. It might almost
even sound like you don't get you you
have very few people that genuinely see
you
>> see what you're doing and just give you
that appreciation. They're not trying to
understand. They're not trying to give
you they just well done you you get only
a few of that. So I had that thing to be
say to say that I'm fine with it
>> like I'm fine with whatever you see me
and whatever perception comes maybe I'm
not serious with my pastoring or I'm not
serious with my career or my business
whatever on seriousness version you have
of me I'm okay with it you'll be fine
and I was I was I was really good with
it and I think with that it just because
at the end of the day everybody's life
is different and some people might try
to project their opinions on you or what
they feel is right which they have the
right because it's their experience So
somebody that has always pastored in a
church where they living cannot see why
you will successfully pastor outside the
church and somebody else that has only
been working or only has a business
would say that anything you're doing you
have to give your there's some truth in
what everybody has to say but at the end
of the day like the theme of this
meeting is what has said about you and
what is God saying to what is your own
script because if you've used somebody
else's script then you see that you are
just in the middle you don't even you're
just floating because you are trying to
get so much so what has God And I think
that was that's settling that for me
that it would take time for people to
understand. But if I'm waiting for
everybody to understand, there will be
so many regrets. Time would have gone. I
won't do the things I want to do. And
>> that's something I had to be okay with.
>> Thank you. Let's pastor Victor go next.
[applause]
>> Um Okay. So cost
>> I I think I'm with what you said. I'm
like on the other side, right? So I
finished um first and foremost I studied
pharmacy. So when you are done with a
course like that, the idea is more you
go out and you go and burn. So imagine
when I'm done with internship and my
guys ask me yeah guys where are we going
to I said God said I stay in Koru you
say you know everybody like you where
you know someone asking me where is
don't [laughter] like don't don't do
that and it was so strong stay where you
are so I started up a I I got a job and
I started working while I was also you
know in church and all of that and at
some point after working that that job
got to got to my neck like my boss was
after my life at some point. So like
Lord I think this is the sign where I
think I have to leave this place and go
and just focus on ministry JJ or maybe
even leave you. I think I've tried and
so in that season funny enough
shout out to my pastor Pastor Edmund by
the way. So he he was having a
conversation with me that he just called
randomly and said when are you leaving
this job? I said, "I'm working on it,
sir." Like, you know, "Good morning. How
are you doing?" Just when are you
leaving this job? I'm working on it.
Okay, that was the end of the
conversation.
>> And so, I put in my resignation letter,
>> not knowing where I was going to get the
next job.
>> Just put in and said, "Okay, you know
what?" Because, by the way, my boss
liked me but didn't like me. So, I just
said, "Okay, you know what? I'm going to
be out of this place but I want to give
you three months so that you know you
can get a replacement.
>> Yeah.
>> Now in my mind I was always I always
felt after that three months I'm going
straight to church and I know that I'm
giving my I'm depositing my full self to
to church. Just give him Exactly. Right.
And so one day I and P were having a
conversation and he just it was just a
random nothing spectacular and he was
like if you leave pharmacy
anyone who is going to go in health
would they believe that you someone can
be in ministry and also be in healthcare
>> and it just stay with me. It was again
the most random conversation
>> and I went back home and I was that's
true.
>> If I leave this place, would I be able
to have a conversation and say you can
do both actually?
>> Yeah.
>> Because there's this con there's this
maybe not everybody that has it, but
there's this idea that if you are in
health, healthcare is the most stressful
thing because sometimes you do 24-hour
calls, you do 48 hour calls. I've done
calls two days and I'm finishing by 8:00
a.m. and by 8:30 I'm going straight to
church
>> and then when I'm done maybe rest for a
few hours by Monday I'm back to work.
>> And so when he said that to me I just
took it up in prayer and God said what
he said is exactly what I want you to
do.
>> Absolutely.
>> And so within that moment two things
happened. I got a job offer where I was
going to head a full department myself.
I was going to literally do everything
and at the same time don't don't judge
me.
>> We listen.
>> We don't judge. Okay. So, I was in a
relationship, wonderful relationship
while also obviously there was ministry.
And so, it looked like perfect. Get this
job, continue your relationship, serve
God, everything in place.
>> And then, you know, when Jesus said, "If
you want to build a house, you will
count the cost."
Within two months, I declined that
offer. I resigned from my job and there
was a breakup.
>> Hold on. Hold on.
>> And then just say, "Lord, if this is it,
we go."
>> The month after I was called up to HSC,
it was the same month Dr. K came around
where he went on apostolic tour.
>> Okay?
>> Right.
>> And I was like, I'm not really
interested in jam. I'm interested in Dr.
K's store. that what I want to go and do
in my life. But a friend said shi they
are calling people let's go right
because they called for an interview
coincidentally I was not called my
friend was called though I applied and
he said if they didn't call you let's go
>> like nothing we went read the exam then
I was called up
>> I said I was not looking for a job like
not you people but okay so I went there
continued by the time I was done they
were calling people to resume they
didn't call me so I felt
I I was not looking for it. So just two
days before going to join Dr. K and all
of that
>> I got called up come and resume.
>> So now the idea is if you are called up
you are supposed to resume immediately.
I said I don't want to resume
immediately. I have something to do
>> and the president said okay go when
you're ready come back.
Are you I are you sure? Okay let just
go. Now coincidentally everybody
resumed. I went, I came back and I
resumed when I was supposed to resume.
>> So if you're asking me what has it cost
me, I think on top of that list would be
relationships. Not just romantic. I mean
people,
>> people not understanding people. When
you say I want to do this, this is what
God is telling me to do. This is where
God is telling me to go to. And like are
you okay in the head? This is not
conventional places you're supposed to
be usual.
>> Exactly. So but then again, if you know
this is what God told you, just do it.
>> No, nobody.
Thank you.
>> Wow. Why am I the last person?
[laughter]
Okay. You know, John 3:16 says, "For God
to love the world that he gave." And if
I have to put it in another words, for
God to love the world that he gave and
he was pained.
>> God giving was something that what God
gave because he loved was a painful. It
was it could almost be said to equate
pain. So what has this thing cost as in
where have I had to Okay, now let me
rephrase it. Um my own experience with
God has been a case of being able to
still stay on God's love and go through
pain.
>> Wow.
>> And being able to look at people and
love them despite what they've done,
what you're going through.
>> Still being able to be the love that
people would experience.
>> Fine. I'm not I at a point I probably
lost some of that ability to love but I
remember far back as being in Eph when
Dr. used to come and I used to when they
said mock I give a testimony I said my
own testimony is that I just want to go
up to God and give God a kiss I just
want to pay God I would say there was a
lot of love you know and there was a
time when people come to church you're a
stranger I walk up there was something
about me just saying you know what I'm
going to be the love people would
experience people see me and they
experience love
>> but then being able to say you know what
there's a pain sometimes the people I'm
even loving are the ones causing the
pain but still being able to say you
know what love is the way to relate with
anybody and everybody. So
>> in summary, what it has cost me is that
ability to still love
>> despite
>> as God has loved even while in pain,
despite the pain and even through pain.
>> Okay, please hold on to that. This
question is going to everyone and I want
us to make it as um brief as possible.
Um the question is u what did you have
to say no to permanently or for a season
in order to say yes to your scripts?
>> What have I had to say no to going with
a trend? I'm in food packaging and
there's a lot happening in Nigeria.
There's a lot this is what everybody is
selling now. This is what they're doing
now.
>> But being able to say that you know what
God how do I what do you want me to do?
I remember um several instances I I can
give without taking too much time doing
things being the only person that is
doing it. I have a masters from
University of Manchester but I sell Gary
I sell Kouly Kouli I sell Kokuro. Hello.
So I know my mom is so hungry but she
there's something she says that you and
God you and God there's a way God
handles you because they're like this is
what you have chosen to do
>> and you and the God proves himself God.
So when you tell people who have masters
to stand up and they're standing up, I
won't be feeling guilty.
No, no, no, no, no, no. So being able to
say no to what everybody's doing, I
before I I left the corporate world, I
was I was the HR manager that people
will call, Tony Lum will call, I get
calls from the UK. I never applied for
jobs. I was being head haunted.
>> Wow.
>> It's nothing that you now went from
there to being in the market space and
rolling with Gary women. So what I've
had to say no to is doing what
everybody's doing or being where
everybody is being and just being able
to go back to God and say God what is
the next thing? I know pastor used to
say that who can believe that you are
selling nylons, you're selling diary
[laughter]
and you you're doing this much and like
>> I can't I can't explain why but I can
just say that it's being able to say yes
to God only.
>> Wow.
>> Only and that works for me.
>> Yeah. Deacon, please go next.
>> Okay. So what I stopped doing, right?
>> Yeah. You said no to permanently up for
a season in order to say yes to your
script.
>> Okay. So I think for me will be so I'm
I'm a career person. I'm a 9 to5 and a 5
to9 person if you get if [laughter] you
get that. So I think it's about looking
for shortcuts
>> while doing what you need to do and
giving less of yourself on both
spectrum.
>> Wow. So I don't I don't think I give
less of myself on whether I'm doing a 9
to5 or I'm doing whatever I'm doing
after my my 5:00 p.m. work. That may
look so simple but it takes a lot of of
energy out of you. You don't want to
show up um less prepared halfbaked
right and you don't want to get into the
trend of this is what everybody in my
career space is doing and I would get
into it. I think the current space I am
in now why we are still less than how
many in the world or even in Nigeria
that practice it when I got in people
still don't understand didn't understood
why what what does it mean even I still
have to explain to people what you do
the way you tell somebody you're a
doctor you're a lawyer I don't think I
can explain [laughter] what I what I do
so so two things is um being prepared at
all times so I think that scripture
about see a man who is diligent in his
work.
>> Diligence is something. So I don't want
to I've rejected things because I know I
am not prepared for them.
>> I've rejected offers because I know look
it is not the time.
>> I've rejected deals that I know I'm not
instructed to pick it up or take it at
that point in time.
>> So it's not about how good the deal is,
it's about what's God saying. Hold on
sir. Yes sir.
>> Okay. Thank you. So similar to um
agreeing I guess um on this part you
just need to stand for integrity
especially if you're in the financial
service so the opportunities to get
tempted so you really have to say no to
a lot of things and I guess I've also
sort of had to reject a lot of job
offers uh one maybe I think will derail
me I think it's going to demand more of
my time and not allow me give so much to
ministry so
>> I guess you never stop saying no and um
what what I guess the motivation will be
or the inspiration will because you have
a calling and you should prioritize that
above every every other thing.
>> Absolutely. Thank you, Pastor Top.
>> Maybe I should just like stay with my
other points. What I've been able to say
no to is um allowing people because we
live because of the time we live in how
the internet is and there are so many
opinions. I think I've been able to say
no to anything that is like outside of
how certain I am with God direction.
That's just it for me.
>> Um so for me I think it's
um you know as it comes wisdom I guess
but it's
watching opinions people's opinions.
A lot of time people will come up and
say, "Oh, I think you should do this. I
think you should do that." And honestly,
they're not necessarily trying to
derail. Sometimes they're coming from a
place of care.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But just as how Jesus was telling Peter
that guy, I might die or this and this
happen. And Peter said, "Hey, no." And
just said, "I know it's care, but what
you're saying it's not should it's the
devil." And so in as much as people
might feel okay why are you in do ah
doing ministry doing um pharmacy is not
stressful do you get it sounds like here
but the truth is if you let it get to
you just a bit you wake up one day and
see that
>> you are you're out of purpose you've
drifted you are you are you become maybe
lazy you become passive that kind of
thing so it's watching
>> those people's opinions basically
I think if you want to follow your
script, people's opinion does not really
matter. It's about what God is saying.
And I think it should it would almost
just be the same thing everyone is
saying because I had I've had to stand
my ground with family. I've had to stand
my ground with um with mentors that love
me. I remember when I told my mentor
that I want to relocate my business from
Aurora, then I had something in school.
I was one of the guy I've started
fashion from school. So they kind of
know me in a career at that level that I
that I was and I wanted to relocate
everything down to Ibadon because God
said follow the last command go back to
Ibadon. So it does not really make sense
at that time I was assisting my campus
pastor then. So I remember pastoring
told me you have to come and tell me
>> that's what God tell what God told you
before you can move and I think for that
everyone's script is it's peculiar and
the ability to say respectfully without
clash unless it get to a place where you
have to really stand firm but you really
don't need people opinion and you have
to follow what God is saying per time I
Sir.
>> All right. What more do I have to say?
They've said it all.
>> All right. So, I'm not going to say
anything different from what everybody
has said. I think this um the same is my
um I I experienced the same as well. I
think one of the things um I I also had
to say no to was opinions like they've
said. I remember after NYC and I was
going back to for ministry. My dad
looked at me like on your own.
[laughter]
literally and then I had nothing just my
transport fair and uh you know but that
season was a you know beautiful season
it was a training ground for me and you
know I had to I've had to also say no to
trends and to offers as well um there
was a time the jackpot trend was you
know popular and um I was really under
pressure even for my parents to say guy
what are you doing you're into tech you
there are a lot of opportunities out
there even in ministry I even got offers
to pastor a church maybe in the US or
something. I'm like I don't there's
nothing in me that is
>> you know there's nothing
you know in no jail in no jail
[laughter]
you know. So these are the things I've
had to say no to to just you know um say
yes to God and then follow his plan for
my life.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Yeah. Everybody had the same it's like
the same um feedback the same thing to
say but in different ways. And I'm sure
that you're able to get one or two
things from that space. So I have two
more questions but um this one please
can I have the microphone? I would like
um Dickin Baby um and to Jimmy and
Pastor D want to just briefly just touch
on this right. Um if you could go back
and sit with yourself at the age of some
of the people in this room. Um what is
the one thing you would say that uh
nobody told you?
[laughter]
Don't worry.
No,
>> me. I'm still young. So,
>> I know. I know. [laughter] I know. Don't
worry.
>> Why should I go back?
>> Well,
no regrets. So,
>> no no no missed time, no lost moments,
anything, anytime. So, there was a
there's a there's a prayer I pray. Well,
not every day. You know, when people say
I pray, it's like you pray it every day.
But there's a there's a prayer that
maybe when we um I'm impressed it's
prayed on my heart to to pray it is
everything I have lost I will recover it
right so I don't think there is anything
I will go back to the fact when I look
at it is a flip side
>> I wanted to study medicine I didn't get
medicine I got biochemistry I wanted to
finish biochemistry go back to study
medicine and my brother looked at me I
said that means when you are graduating
I will also be graduating I said okay
I'm not going back [laughter]
and I was having an
I will not wait for you go and do
medicine how many years I said okay
>> okay sorry
>> I was in a relationship okay so
>> so what what what why I said that it
looks funny is that
>> there is no regret of not going to study
medicine
>> the day where I was I have a friend one
my my best friend is actually um pastor
Tommy knows My best friend is a lecturer
in Futa. He's a PhD holder. The day we
compare notes, I told him, I said, not
bragging. I think I'm earning more than
your professor.
>> Wow.
>> And if I had followed the career path I
crafted for myself until God opened my
eyes to it during internship,
>> I think I won't have gone according to
the plan of God. So that I said I won't
look back and say I should have done
this. rather I will look back and say
how I wish I had listened early enough
>> to have clarity
>> I didn't get clarity on what I was going
to do until 400 level
>> I was a top of my class I was acing
biochemistry and everything now I don't
know jack about the structure again but
as at 400 level clarity as at graduation
going to serve and the instruction of
don't work your posting
clarity
>> go to go to the east. I went to Abba
when Aba was abba
>> and I did not do trade. I did not do
business rather I went there to
rediscover myself right. So I will not
look back and say how I wish I rather I
would say how I wish I had known the
same way some of you knew from 100 level
when you were joined school got
admission me I didn't year jack until
400 500 level so it's that's where I'll
put it
>> okay so I'll just read what God told me
when I was younger at least that's the
question what would I say to them from
Isaiah 48
>> and it says um this is what the Lord
says from verse 17 your redeemer the
only one of Israel. I'm the Lord your
God who teaches you what is good for you
>> and leads you along the path you should
follow
>> all that you have listened to my
commands. Then you'd have had peace
flowing like a gentle river and
righteousness rolling over you like
waves in the sea. Your descendants
because your descendants are ahead of
you would have been like the sands along
the seashore too many to count. There
would have been no need for your
destruction or for cutting off your
family name.
>> Wow.
>> So that is what I would say to you. If
you don't listen to God, if you don't
listen to his commandments, then the
likelihood that there will be some
destruction along the line and it might
affect your family name is very strong.
It's very high.
>> So the summary, you and God, you are
enough.
>> So God,
>> you and God you are.
>> Okay. So if I'm to sort of speak to
people in the room, one, I would say
that there shouldn't be any regrets.
time doesn't matter whether you are
behind. Um my story is that I spent nine
years in school. So I sort of lost about
5 years in school and um I was restored.
So don't live in regrets. Anything can
still happen regardless of whatever
where you are at the moment.
>> I say you need to have an open mind. Um
like I thought I was just going to be in
ministry. Um so I sort of love the
concept of this. You can be in ministry
and so be in the marketplace. Back in
the days, marketplace wasn't such much
of a concept. In those days, I would
tell you, oh, you called to minister.
Why? Why you doing in the banking
sector? You're wasting your time. More
like they're guilt tripping you.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But now things have changed. So
have an open mind. Um be exposed.
>> Um sometimes people in ministry, they're
not exposed. People in the career space,
they're not exposed. So to expand your
mind, expose your mind. And that comes
through relationship, that comes through
the books that you read, that comes
through what you listen to. So you can
actually travel farther than even being
um locally. Um
>> yeah. So and follow God, which is the
most important thing. Um please follow
God. It might seem very unpopular. It
might seem as if you're making a
mistake. It might seem as if people are
going ahead of you. Sometimes like a
catapult. You're pulling back and you're
about to just launch forth. So just just
just follow God.
>> Praise God. Um we have so many more
questions but we will not be able to
take them because our time is fast spent
but I want to understand that um a lot
that has been said today has gone
somewhere and sew some seed in your
hearts that it's not about um it's not
about what people are saying it's not
about the opinion of others it's about
what God is saying sit with God you know
that's what everybody has said they've
all said this at one point or the other
that what matter most is what is God
telling you. It doesn't matter what
mommy's saying, daddy's saying, uncles,
anybody are saying is what is God
telling you. And I hope that as you
leave here today, you will put that very
close to your hearts that what is God
telling me. And now will you know that
you know that in the place of prayer,
you know that in the place of fellowship
um with Holy Ghost joy. Can you
appreciate our pastors, our leaders?
Thank you sir. Thank you ma. We
appreciate you. Praise God.
>> Hallelujah. So we'll continue um in
scripts and scrolls. You make welcome
the choir.
Come on, let's jump for Jesus one more
time. Jams for Jesus. Wonderful time.
Amen.
Jam your hands. It's too much. Jam your
hands for God to give you life. Come on.
Jam your hands for Jesus.
God.
Uh Jesus said that I have come that they
may have life and have life in.
Okay, let us revise that. I have come
that they may have life and have life in
him. Okay. Who is he talking to? Who are
those he talking to? Is it me alone? If
you know Jesus is talking to you, trust
that yes, give me life in abundance.
Amen. That is a living life. So we are
going to um a song of our father faith
Dr. K titled Zoe Life. Come on J for
Jesus.
Glory to God.
So now to bring you up to speed, we are
going to teach you the song, right?
We're going to teach you ament of the
song. Relax. You're father's house. Your
father's house. Yeah. Nothing's going to
happen to you, right? Come on. Just
back. Relax. Right. So the the song is
Zoe Life, right?
Ready?
We are the We are the choirs. We the
choirs. We're going to do it now. It's
not hard. We can do all through Christ.
Who? We can do all things through Christ
who what?
So you just move your body where you
are. Come on. Let the spirit. Let it
shake. You're not still. You're not a
wood. There's something living in you
now. You get it.
So be going on two 3 2 go.
So it's a very simple one. Are ready?
Let's go. Come on.
Let me see this part. This one. See
first. So this is it.
That's the one part. I'm going to teach
you a little one now.
And it shows who he shows.
A simple one.
[music]
Can you do that for me?
So he shows in me. Some people some
people are this side. They're not
getting it. Two, three, go.
And it shows
now listen.
and it shows. Oh, it shows Zoe. Do you
understand?
And it shows
where to go.
Fire 2 3 go.
>> Ze
>> overflowing. [music and singing]
>> Can't you see
>> no more li
>> I am free. God can inside of me [music]
in
>> overflowing
falling. [singing]
>> I am free.
>> God can life [music] of me. So that's
the teach.
>> Are we there now? That's me want you
right. Let's
go.
Life in me.
Let's relax. Are you ready?
I going now. I go two. Let's go. [music]
[singing]
>> Overflowing.
>> Can't you see?
>> No more li [music]
inside of me.
[singing]
>> Life in me.
>> Overflowing.
>> Can't you see?
>> Can you understand?
>> So, we're [music] going now. Let's go.
This is not survival. [music]
This is the way the god kind of
>> this is not [music]
the god kind of
>> everything but
you [music] caught me out of the night.
Now I'm living in your light.
>> No more
>> no more.
>> No more [music] chasing.
>> What would it mean?
>> For the life you gave.
>> Now I'm rolling in all different
[music and singing] lane. us who is the
Christ. This life know my voice.
>> What you gave
>> I [music and singing] receive.
>> Now your life is flowing free.
>> Life in me. [music]
>> Overflowing. [singing]
>> No more living.
>> I am free.
>> God can life [music] inside of me.
[singing]
>> I shine.
>> I shine. [music]
>> It's no beyond.
>> We rise. [singing]
Now I'm leaving [music]
from the
>> not brand new. This life I live is
coming from you. Not by works nor what I
do with me. I live in
[music and singing] full.
>> I don't have to.
>> What you [music and singing]
fullness
>> is not precious
>> is divine
from this [music and singing] side.
Every breath
>> living.
[music and singing]
>> No more living.
>> I am free. [music]
>> What kind life inside of me? [singing]
>> I shine. I
[music]
>> from day
>> river
now I'm living from the ground [music]
where they come from
>> waiting now.
[singing and music]
>> Yes.
in me.
>> I know
in me
>> ever living life in me. River.
[music]
And he shows who we [music]
[singing]
>> are.
And he shows who we should be. glory.
[music and singing]
[music]
>> I want to thank you for
>> now we have a picture of it now.
Yeah.
Yeah. Come on. This is not survival.
This is [music] the way the God kind of
life.
>> This is the survival. [music]
>> This is hope.
>> I was ready, but I was in the light.
Hope you f [music]
you me out of the night. I am living in
your life.
>> No more driving,
>> no [music] more,
>> no more chasing.
>> I know
from the life you made. [music]
>> I am running.
[singing]
is not bright. [music]
>> It's life.
>> I'm so
[music]
over.
>> Can't you see?
>> I am free. But every of [music]
[singing]
>> I shine
>> I shine [music]
[singing]
>> I'm with
the
not brand new. This life I leave is
coming from you. Not by
me.
have been raised into this life.
>> Was you finished?
>> I [music] am
>> and I am fullness.
>> Your precious
[music]
>> life
is working.
>> Overflowing.
>> No more [music] living.
>> I am free.
>> God [singing] can light me.
I shine
>> I [music] shine
>> all night
>> from winning.
>> We're going the last one. Come on.
from inside
[music]
>> enough
river.
Come on.
[singing]
>> Join us and sing this high.
[music]
[singing]
Sorry,
>> sorry,
>> sorry.
Everywhere we go, [music]
>> and everything you touch,
>> and everything you do,
[music and singing]
>> in the morning, [music and singing]
>> in the noon time,
>> in [singing]
where you go, [music]
>> every day
What you wear?
[music]
[singing]
>> Hey, one more time everybody.
[music]
[singing]
>> Come on.
>> So now we got it. Now everybody I want
us to say it together. So we're going to
take it from say
and it shows [music] it shows
last time. Let's go.
Let's go.
And it shows [music] glory. It shows
glory. Come on. J for J for Jesus. Glory
to God.
Celebrate Jesus in this place.
Is Jesus you are celebrating his meal?
Somebody celebrate Jesus in this place.
I think we need to take that song again.
Are we ready?
>> [music]
>> He never submit a song.
By the way, that's one of the songs of
Dr. Ko.
Dr. K has released about seven albums in
the last one month.
You better celebrate Dr. K. He might be
watching also
for real. And perhaps you're wondering
where you can get those songs from. If
you go to your In fact, can we do that
now? Let's go to everybody pick out your
phone. Go to Spotify if you do have it
on your phone. If you don't download
Spotify.
So if you go on Spotify,
search for Alia K.
Althia. A L E T H I A
L E T H I A then space K K K K K K K K K
K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K K
K K K K K K K K K K K K A A Y, Alia K. I
mean, Dr. K's got some some amazing
songs.
Yeah, about seven in one week. in one
week. I don't know where Dr. K is
getting the energy from. I you know
sometimes I'm asking myself am I the one
chasing Dr. K. I mean I should have
energy more than but sometimes like Baba
let me just be following your footstep
like this
and Dr. K you know I'm I'm releasing
like four albums like four albums. Do
you know what an album?
Do you know what an album is? They're
releasing four albums. And you know,
it's one thing back to what I was saying
earlier, it's one thing to to release
songs. It's another thing to release
them excellently.
Have you seen Artha
on on um Spotify, please? Um is it
follow? Have you subscribed? What do
they use on Spotify? I think it's
follow, right? So that's that's our
Father in the Faith album. I mean, he's
got about seven albums, if not up to
nine now. There's Overflow. There is
Unshaken.
Pardon me. Those two, I I fell in love
with those two. So, I'm yet to visit the
other ones. But those two, I don't play
and tire. This particular ones, oh, my
daughter knows it more than my wife. I'm
sorry. I'm not
Imagine going to school on a on a Monday
morning. I know that
you
can do something together. I want us to
sing that song together. I like that
song. Choir, you help me. You don't have
to come up stage. Just stay where you
are. projection. Can we do that lyrics
again? I want us to know that song. I
mean, those those are words.
Zoe. Oh, it shows in me. You know what
Zoe means? The very life of God.
Are we together? Zoe is what? Is the
very life of God in you. I mean, those
are revelations.
Those are revelations. There's a
particular one that that that's on that
um I don't know if it's on on shaking or
overflow. That one is Psalm 91. Oh boy.
Don't worry. You can sit down. Just so
can we do it together?
Okay. In fact, I think we should stand
up. Let's stand up and let's do it
together. Everybody, let's stand up.
Let's stand up. It's our father song. We
are going into another session though.
But before I want us to I want us to be
body to that song is is be bodyable. He
is what?
G. What's up?
Hey.
You're not moving. They're not moving.
Until you move, I will not we will not
sing it.
See, wait. Wait. One thing you
understand is all those your fire boy
what do you call it burner boy I I can't
somebody calling themselves bunner it's
not my business this song is sweeter
than those song
I'm serious
those songs they don't have life in them
how somebody I
sing them you declare life into yourself
I say I fall for that step Elizabeth are
ready in fact I think we We should do
some dance moves. Eh, can we do it?
Are we ready? Where's Gift?
>> Is Gift still in this house? Where is
she?
Gift, where are you now?
Come and help my life now. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come and teach us on
Can you give us like one or two? Don't
worry. Don't worry. You're on duty
before your guy will cut my head. Are we
ready right now?
Zo, I hope I got it. Can we get
everybody?
[singing]
>> Let's just for 1 2 3 Let's go.
>> He's just
Can I hear these people? Let me hear
you.
>> Let me hear them now. 3 4 go.
>> Okay,
that energy is on. Any pastors? One,
two, let me hear you say
their energy is not strong. Yeah.
One, two, let's go. Sing.
>> I want to stay here.
>> Are we ready? 3 2 1 Hey! Imagine
[music]
this this table is up to that table and
they don't feel energy
everybody. Zoe Zoe choir, are you ready
to help us now? 1 2 3 let's go. Zoe Zoe
God kind of life.
Please help me now.
>> This is Come on. [music]
Let's go again. Zoe. Come on, let's go.
>> Again
kind of life.
>> I was but I was in the light. Moving
fast empty. Then you called me out of
the night. Now I'm living in your light.
>> No more drying.
[music]
>> They were from the cross.
>> Now I'm running in different lane. is no
hle
>> what you gave. I receive
>> now your life they flow in me
[music and singing]
>> so
>> life in me
>> overflowing you see
>> me
>> I am free
>> God's kind life inside of me
[music]
>> I'm talking
again. [music]
I want
>> understand this entropy. I want us to
know that chorus well. See, once we know
the chorus, other one we'll be learning
as we listen to the song.
Are you ready? Right now
1 2
[music]
>> no [singing] more me.
>> I am free. God can life inside of me
>> zing zing
>> overflowing. Can't you see?
>> No more.
>> I am free.
>> God can life inside of me.
Zing [music]
life in me overflowing.
[singing]
>> I am free.
>> No more life inside of me.
life in me.
>> Okay.
God
of me
life in me overflowing. [singing]
[music]
>> No more limited.
>> I am free.
>> God can life inside of me again.
>> Overflowing.
>> Can't you see? [music and singing]
>> No more limit. I am free.
>> God can life inside of me.
EVERYBODY 1 2 3 LET'S GO.
Life in me [music and singing]
overflowing.
>> Can't you see? No more.
God
of me.
Life in me overflowing. Can't you see?
Come on.
>> I am free.
>> God [music and singing]
life inside of me.
Two more times. Life in me overflowing.
[music and singing]
>> No more lizo.
Zoe. Life in me overflowing. Can't you
see it? No more limit. No more limit.
>> I am free.
>> I am free. God inside of me.
>> Are you ready? 3 2 Ze
>> life in me overflowing.
>> Can't you see no more me?
>> I am free.
>> God can life inside of me. Zoe Zoe life
[music] in me overflowing.
>> Can't you see no more me?
>> I am free.
>> God can life inside of me.
[music]
>> Overflow right now. I am
God inside of me.
>> Hold on.
>> Audience, let me hear you.
>> 3 2 Z
life in me.
>> Can't you see no more in me inside of
me? Zoe, Zoe. Life in me.
>> Overflowing life in me.
>> Life in me.
Can you see?
>> Can't you see? No more limits. Can't you
see?
>> 3 2
>> overflowing. Can't you see?
>> No more limit.
>> I am free. God can life inside.
[music]
>> Overflowing.
>> Can't you see?
>> No more limit. I am free. God can life
inside
[singing]
[music]
overflowing.
>> I am free.
>> God [music and singing] can life inside
of me.
>> Come on.
One more time. [singing]
>> Sing it out loud.
>> Last time.
>> Can we celebrate the grace of God upon
our father? He can hear you. I think
he's watching us. Can you celebrate our
father in the faith? I mean those are
amazing [music] words. All right, I have
one short assignment here. You can sit
down for a moment.
That that was that was quite an
exercise. Imagine if you play that song
for
if you're going for money juggle just
plugging be jogging life. Uh
all right, Kingswood youth, are you in
the house? Ah, you're not sounding like
it. Kingswood Youth, are you in the
house?
>> Kingswood Youth, are you in the house?
>> So, I will know you're in the house. So,
I will call your installation. So, I I
give me a response. I could know if you
inside the house or not. Kingswood Youth
EA. Are you in the house?
>> Ah, you guys are sleeping. You're not in
the house. Imagine your host is not in
the house. Imagine when the host is not
in the house. What will the visitor do?
Youth, are you in the house?
It be like 10 of them come
youth, are you in the house?
>> VI youth, are you in the house? Okay,
they're on their way.
Aquet, are you in the house?
I've been looking for them since.
Where's that auntie that did? Where's
auntie? Are you asking me to shout? Hey,
I catch you. Hey, what's that? What's
that video again? I I don't laugh tired.
You're making noise. I'm making noise.
Please celebrate a church for me.
Are you in your house?
Imagine say they come meet you for
you in the house.
Are you in the house?
Ah, come on in the house.
Oh, I feel him.
Let's take it again in the house.
Oh, that that voice is is piercing.
Okay, I dare you.
Oh, Corba, are you in the house? Ah, you
they fight me. Say yes sir.
Where are you?
You follow me. Fight. Are you in the
house?
You mean like they they're too they're
posh. They're posh people. All right.
Please celebrate every installation in
the house this afternoon.
Um it's it's quite so the session we
find ourselves we call it the youth
connect.
You know this is king's word right? Who
are we? Ah you're not sure. Who are we?
>> Do you even know your creed? Can we do
our creed together? 1 2 3 go.
>> Tell me something.
Come on.
[screaming]
>> Yay.
Tell me are you
>> let me [screaming] hear you.
>> I am king.
[cheering]
>> IF YOU LOVE THIS STUFF, [screaming] COME
ON.
>> HEY.
OH, this is taught.
>> This is taught.
So we're going to do something right for
some of you have been in Kingswood for 5
years, 10 years. I mean for me standing
I've been in Kingswood for 14 years from
days.
Yeah. For some people in this auditorium
from the day they were given birth up
until now they've been in King's World.
Amen. I'm serious. I mean Kings is going
to be 30 something years. Uhhuh. It's
not a joke. And some of you 20 years
whatever and for some of you is just one
month ago. You're welcome. This is home.
Can can we give them a warm welcome for
those?
So we're going to do something. You know
um one one vital moment that I don't
want you to joke with is this moment. We
need to blend. Who believe that? I
should be able to see a Kingswood
member, not necessarily in Ka, not
necessarily in Aquaba, but at the mall,
at the supermarket,
at boardroom, and there's this love.
Kings were a love church. Are we
together? Am I lying? I mean, that's the
kings of me. I know. I don't the king
that you know, the one me I know. So,
but but you know, [laughter]
I don't know if you know, but the king
of me I know, I love church. So I I want
us to be able to bond beyond
installations. Are we together? Beyond
installation, beyond um campuses, we
should be able to meet ourselves in
places and just imagine
Elizabeth, please come. By the way, I
got to know Elizabeth virtually and we
have bonded. Imagine that's King for
you. Imagine um Elizabeth is trying to
buy something here in a mall and I'm
also coming like I am King George. I
love this church. In fact, can we do
that? Look at the person behind you or
beside you. Come down. 1 2 3 go. Let's
go. I AM KINGD AND I LOVE THIS.
>> SEE, I'm and that's the energy I want us
to leave this room with.
>> Yes, sir.
>> It's time we spread the gospel of this
church.
>> Am I am I lying please? I mean you tell
like is lying. [laughter]
How I should be able to bomb say I am
made a talk say in kings we are not
normal.
Pastor T we say me I'm mad we are making
a difference in we are making a
>> that's who we are SO
I AM KING AND [screaming] I LOVE THIS
CHURCH HOW YOU DONE WITH MY sister
haven't you realize all those white
people don't let me go too far
and you will be they don't know each
other from but the fact that they can
recognize white white but guess what in
king word we and recognize his
supernatural army. WE CAN RECOGNIZE THAT
WE ARE KINGS AND WE HAVE NO TASTE FOR
MEN RELIGION WITHOUT TAINT. I AM KINGS
>> AND I LOVE THIS CHURCH.
>> Are we together?
>> That's the culture we are going to be
from this place. So in the next few
minutes we going to switch. You're not
leaving your chair but you're leaving
your chair. What I mean is you still
come back to your table. But I want you
to everybody stand up. Everybody stand
up. Stand up. Stand up. Stand up. Let's
do this. We need to know ourselves
beyond um projection. Are you ready with
my questions? You I want us to know
ourselves beyond insolation, beyond the
only time we should be meeting is not
just when we come together like this. Do
you know that one conversation can birth
a solution that will solve a wide
problem and they will tell you ah oh my
kings
I'm serious
they product king people that they do
for their church they produce the time
for us to start producing is now the
time for us to start shining that light
is now
I always remember the first time I saw
Dr. K. He sang a song. Come on. Come on.
Song. This little light of mine.
But Dr. K did something to me that
night. I will never forget. He might not
even remember. He just said, "Shut up.
What little light? This massive light of
mine.
I'm going to let it shine. This
massive." And from that night more me I
don't carry little light. OH, I CARRY
MASSIVE LIGHT.
Are we together? So the more the
brighter
it's not marrier don't worry we are we
will marry but the more
>> are we together right now so you're
going to leave your your seat please
carry your phone we don't have anybody
still in this space no that's not the
reason I say carry your phone is so that
you can I mean exchange contact and all
those you get what I'm saying right now
so carry your [music] phone I want you
to go around and meet somebody you have
never met before I'm not saying in your
installation
can we borrow
What do you want to borrow?
Talk to me now. Don't worry. Camera will
not come to you.
What do you want to borrow? Are we
together? So, I want you to leave your
seats. Okay. So, go around. I want you
to meet at least two people. Let's start
with one person first. Meet somebody
that you have never met before. Are we
ready right now? Now, let's hit the ball
rolling very fast. And what you're going
projection, please help me with the
first question. I need you to know them.
Know their name.
projection. Do you have my question? So,
look at the screen. No, no, no, no, no,
no. Pastor Tumi and my wife, you know
yourself. We've been together from about
day. So, that's not what I'm talking
about.
My wife and Adura, you know yourself.
Come on. Meet somebody. I've never
Please you guys are doing like you have
seen me before. Nobody's coming to meet
me. Adura, I know you now. But still
come
now. G. Hello. Sh. Now, not just me.
Look at the question on the screen. What
is a small thing that instantly makes
your day better? Oh yeah, discuss that
in 5 minutes. Oh, somebody said
I are we ask I ask you question
somebody new.
Why are you meeting yourself on that
table? Come on. Come on. Leave that
table.
You see those two guys? What are they
doing on that table? Leave that table
and go around and meet people. See that
question. What is a small thing that
instantly makes your day better?
Come on. Come on.
You never can tell. Oh, maybe this is
where your spouse is.
Call number.
Hey, see those guys. She has a bond.
Leave that corner that you are those
guys. Leave that corner. Enter the crowd
and meet people.
Somebody your wife is in this
auditorium.
That brother on Tai, you're just there.
I know.
Somebody the connect you need to that 1
billion project. Pastor T and Pastor Ti,
you know yourselves.
[laughter]
You know yourself.
He's not God. He's only God. You should
know more.
>> Hi. Hello. Let me meet you.
I like your style. How you doing? It's
good to meet you. I know I've seen you
before, but I'll see you again.
>> Hi. Come on, meet me. How you doing?
>> What's that one small thing that makes
your day better?
>> Me and your friend.
>> What kind of friend?
Okay. So, what's next?
>> What do you guys
>> My brother's name
I will give you two more minutes.
I don't know you before. You're a real
estate agent. You sell land. That's what
you do. I know you.
I know you already. Your name is Sam
Swaj.
You are a real estate agent.
You have land at what's that place
again?
Why are you dancing? Who are you
meeting?
One more minute.
Call number your helper this room.
Don't go and be for me for your helper.
May your helper not pass you by.
Why are you guys standing there? Enter
this crowd. You that you want to marry
next year. Where's your babe? Better go
and find baby in that place.
Enter that place and come.
Let me also come down and meet you.
You're just sitting down there. Why you
standing like this? 30 more seconds.
>> Yes. What? How you doing?
I'm glad you
can't wait to have it.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, come here. Come
here. Come here. Come here. If you
offend me now, I have I have a council.
How do you call it? Council
representative. I know I have a barista.
There's a way you guys use council
something.
>> I have an not the Holy Spirit advocate
is
who
Coca-Cola say if you want free
Coca-Cola. Mr. Guy get up.
It's not easy. It's not used to seven
years in the university.
I don't blow for this church. I swear I
tell you say your belief.
I will not
where are you? Show your face.
Where's the cicero? Show your face.
Why are you hiding your face now?
Where is he now?
Come, come, come, come.
Let me give you one more minute before
we move to the next question.
Maj
Cesero, nice to finally meet you. At
least now I know I have somebody in the
youth church that we are both on, you
know.
>> It's good to meet you. I I learned you
have been discussing me.
>> I can't I can't help you.
>> Okay,
let's move to the next question. So look
for another neighbor that you have not
met. What's the next question? So look
at the screen.
Me alone, I've met about three people.
Three different awesome people. A
barista. Not just a barista in Nigeria.
She even works with a US firm law firm.
Ah more
amaz. Okay. Then I've also met with a
data analyst.
You will tell me who you meet. Okay.
Question number two. Are we together?
Kings. What you thought? Are we
together? Please help me snap those
babes. They even taking selfie together.
That's what I'm talking about. So look
at the next question. They said find
someone new and answer this together. If
you could instantly become excellent at
one random scale, what would it be and
why?
Do you get it? Or you look for somebody
else and discuss that?
Sam, leave that table now.
You have spent too much time on that
table.
Well, after you're done meeting with
him, also make sure you meet somebody
else.
I hope you are meeting your huh those
ones are even doing 10 claps already.
Hey
You have two more minutes for that one.
Meet somebody new.
Hallelujah.
You have one more minute to make sure
you meet somebody new.
My brother, you're standing. You're not
meeting somebody new.
There are so many new persons here they
have not seen before.
>> 10 more seconds.
>> KINGSWOOD YOUTH CHURCH. I AM KINGSWOOD.
>> I AM.
>> We are coming up. We are coming up. I am
King's word.
>> All right, let's come back to our
various seats.
Let's come to our seats. Come to our
seats very fast.
Keep that music on now until they fully
settled.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Come back. Can you see
now? You have met you have met somebody
new now and you have started doing
you can move the to WhatsApp chat
call number
as kings world youth we should see
ourselves outside and you know that bond
is there already
let's come back to our seat
let's come back let's come back let's
come
As you're coming back, I want us to
recite our grid one more time with all
the energy you've got. Are we ready?
Are we ready?
Kings World Youth Church. Are we ready?
At the count of three, we take our creed
again.
As you're coming back to your seat, take
your creed. Are you ready? One, two,
three. Let's go.
>> Louder.
Come to your seat as I reciding.
>> I can't hear you.
>> Can we do it together?
>> Uhhuh.
So that one you now wrap it and put it
in your pocket. Oh yeah, come back. Oh,
we need to move to the next session.
This session is for us to burn. Don't
over bond now. Somebody have find Don't
let me say what I want to say. I'm
seeing one man and one one guy and one
lady they smiling. That smile was not
there before. Shall I bring Sh come and
see us for counseling.
I'm still waiting for Pastor Victor and
the newly
pastor.
Yeah. Meeting that man for the first
time. Okay. Are we ready right now?
Are we ready right now? Are you ready? I
would have loved to start asking you who
you met and all those things but because
of time. So we are going to take our
creed again. Please turn off that music.
Can we rise up on our feet? Yo, please
get ready.
I want us to take our creed like we did
earlier. I know you've met someone new
and you're shacking you. Don't worry.
Even me shack me. I just met you might
see in all of you that I met you're
important. But there's one that is
sweetening me. A barista.
with the barista in Nigeria cost the
barista with a US law firm you see I
don't blow I come meet data analyst join
you you not clap for me
don't worry now all this connect you are
building we're not just doing for fun we
want to actually know ourselves build
bonds you know and build something out
of it all right are you ready can we
take our created with all of our energy
ready one 2 3 let's go
>> ah
Say it louder.
>> Aha.
>> Come on.
Let's go.
Say it like a minute.
Uh-huh.
Come on. LOUDER. LET ME HEAR YOU.
>> Let me hear you.
>> DO YOU LOVE THIS [screaming] CHURCH?
DO YOU LOVE THIS CHURCH? LOUDER. I AM
KING'S LORD.
Come on. Celebrate God's grace in this
house and have your seat in God's
presence. Come on. Come on. You can do
better. Hallelujah. Welcome YCOP.
You're worth of my praise.
You're the King of Kings and the Lord of
Lord.
Oh, we worship you, Jesus.
Thank you, Jesus.
I know [singing]
that worship is about the song you want
to sing. [music and singing]
You're the one I want to sing.
I'm here so you can sing over me.
and I'll sing it [music] back to you.
I [singing] know
that worship is about the song you want
to [music] sing.
You're the one I want
[music and singing] to sing.
I'm here so you can sing over me.
And I [singing] sing it back to you.
Oh.
[singing]
I worship with spirit and truth.
Oh.
[singing]
Oh,
I [music] worship with spirit and truth.
I know,
>> I know [music]
that worship is about the song you want
to [singing] sing.
You're the one I want to sing.
[singing and music]
I'm guessing you can sing over me.
[music]
>> Now [singing] I'll sing it back to you.
Cuz I know
>> I know [music]
>> that worship is about the song [singing]
you want to hear.
>> Not the one I [music] want to sing.
[singing]
I'm here so you can sing [music] over me
and I'll [singing] sing goodbye to you.
[music]
[singing]
Oh
[singing and music]
>> I worship
>> I worship spirit [music]
and truth. say, "Oh, [singing]
[music]
[singing]
>> I worship."
>> I worship [music and singing]
and truth.
>> Say, "I know."
>> I know. [music and singing]
>> Worship
is above me. You want to hear
>> Jesus
the one [music and singing] I want to
sing.
>> I'm here so you can sing [music] over me
and I'll sing [music] it back to you cuz
I know
>> I know [music and singing]
>> that worship is about the song you want
to hear.
You're the [singing] one I want to
[music] see.
I'm here. So you can sing
[music and singing] over me
and I'm singing [music and singing]
about say oh
[music]
[singing]
>> I worship
>> I worship [music]
>> singing Oh,
[music and singing]
>> I worship. I worship [music]
his say, "Oh,
[singing]
[music]
>> I worship. I worship his [music]
[singing]
>> I worship [music]
>> I worship his spirit.
>> Oh Lord my God, how great you are. You
[music] are more than words can say,
more than what my mind can grasp. Oh
Lord my God, how great
[music and singing] you are. You are
more than words can say, more than say.
Oh Lord,
>> oh Lord [music and singing] my God, how
great you are. You are more than one.
[music] Thank you Jesus. More than my
Lord my [music and singing] God, how
great you are. You are more than one
thing. [music]
More than one
[singing] might.
You are more than what [music] can more
than one master [singing]
[music] you are. You are more than one
more than my
Lord my [music and singing] God. How
great you are. You are more than can
[singing]
my love. Oh God,
how [music and singing] great you are.
You are more than words can sing. More
than one
[music and singing]
God. How you are. You are more than can
my mind. [music]
Oh [singing] Lord my God, how great
[music] you are. You are more than one
more than what my mind [music]
[singing]
[music]
can rise up on our feet right now.
>> I worship him [music]
and
>> father we give you the praise. Can we
rest upon our faith? You know while I
was having uh that connect session here
our father in the faith the director of
operation kings of Africa.
Listen listen this was not the energy we
started with. Can we celebrate our
father in the faith
our father in the lord the director of
operations king toward Africa.
He sweetened me. [cheering]
>> Now let me say this to you. Thank you.
I I will be bringing him up right now. I
want you to prepare your heart.
>> Let me share a little bit just few
seconds. Something happened to me last
year and um I was just in my own zone
and
trying to connect one or two but it was
not connected.
Then it dawned on me that I need to make
some readjustment and all of those
things you know and I walked up to
pastor I still remember in the lounge
that day and I know told him I found out
I'm doing this and he said no it's not
you it's the devil and he you know just
give me a fresh perspective said don't
allow the devil and I can tell you not
trying to sugar coat anything from that
day
you know what I believe was that they
would say revival comes and for me
revival has come to stay I'm I've been
sincere with you in my life. I mean, I
saw pastor still move into a new flow.
And I mean, it's going to about 2 years,
3 years now. I'm like, come on. This is
the zone I want to be.
Is somebody ready to this afternoon
with all of the joy on your inside
[cheering] with all of the energy?
Please welcome with me our father, our
pastor,
the director of operation, Kingswood
Africa, PASTOR TODAY.
We can do better. Kingswood youth
church.
Hallelujah.
Glory, glory be to God.
>> I see about half of us are excited to be
here.
>> So help me ask your neighbor, are you
here on your own accord
>> or you are here by force?
Let that neighbor respond. Get a
response.
Let your neighbor know. If you are not
here on your own accord, you're a
suspect. So ask your neighbor, are you a
suspect?
or you are here by your own accord.
Someone that is glad to be in the house
this afternoon, raise your voice one
more time and give the Lord a shout
of praise.
[music]
>> Hallelujah.
>> [screaming]
>> It's it's a joy to be um with the youth
church.
>> I can't remember last time I actually
ministered. I know there was a meeting
you had like two years ago
and it's so it's great to see us going
from strength to strength.
>> How many people understand that we are
in a takeover generation?
>> Yes sir.
>> And you see yourself taking over.
>> Can I hear you? Can I feel you? Say we
are taking over.
Say community to community.
>> Community to community,
>> city to city,
>> to city,
>> nation to nation,
>> nation to nation.
>> Till we reach the ends of the earth.
>> Can you celebrate God one more time?
>> Hallelujah.
>> Lift your hands to him. Father, we give
you praise.
We thank you for this youth conference.
We thank you for what you're doing in
every individual heart, in every
individual life.
Thank you for passing on the pioneering
grace, the pioneering anointing from
generation to generation.
And we thank you that everyone that you
have brought here to yourself, nobody
will live the same way they came.
>> Thank you for a release of fresh grace.
the grace you placed on our father Dr.
Okay. Um, you are passing it on to one
generation after another generation. And
Lord, we are grateful to see that. We
are thankful.
We bless you, Father.
Lift those hands again. And if you can
pray in the Holy Ghost, just begin to
pray in the spirit. Let's align our
hearts aresh again to God just for a few
minutes.
And if you are here for any reason, you
don't pray in the Holy Ghost, you can
just pray in your understanding and ask
the father, Lord, align my heart to your
heart. It's a very simple prayer. Align
my heart to your heart. Align my purpose
for living,
to the purpose for which you created me.
Align my will to your will.
Oh, raise your voice and pray in the
Holy Ghost if you can.
You are faithful. You are good. You are
merciful. You are kind. You are
wonderful. You are excellent.
A thousand tongues, a million tongues, a
billion tongues, a trillion tongues will
not be enough to tell of all that you
have done. We give you praise.
One more minute. Come on, somebody. Pray
in the Holy Ghost and pray fervently if
you can.
[music]
Oh.
We give you praise, Father.
Oh, we bless your name.
Blessed art thou,
son of David.
Blessed art thou root of J.
Can somebody bless the Lord in the house
this afternoon? Oh, blessed thou
son of David.
Blessed art thou [singing]
root of Jes.
You are eminently glorious. You are
[singing] eminently
glorious.
Immaculately beautiful.
[music]
>> We can go on and on and on
and [singing] on. [music]
>> On and on and on.
Oh, but our words are not [music]
enough. [singing]
Our vocabulary will fail.
Permit [music]
us to cry.
I
bow [singing]
[singing]
bow [music]
I bow.
I do.
[music and singing]
>> One more time. You are eminently
glorious. One more time. You are
[music]
>> glorious.
Immaculately beautiful.
>> Oh, we can go. on and on
[music and singing]
and on and on.
But I won't
I [music]
[singing and music]
>> [music]
>> The heart of parity.
Happy.
[music]
[screaming]
You are eminently
glorious,
>> immaculately [music]
beautiful.
>> We can go on and on,
>> on and on.
>> But father, we acknowledge our words are
not enough.
>> Our vocabulary will fail.
[music and singing]
made us cry.
[singing and music]
>> We reverence you in this place. Lord,
we thank you for bringing us into your
kingdom, bringing us into your purpose,
bringing us into your plan, bringing us
into your will,
bringing us into your agenda for such a
time as this.
Thank you that we are not here by
accident
but we are here by divine calling,
divine placement.
We are here because of that which you
want to do, which you intend to do,
which you plan to do.
Your word tells us even these things
were planned before the ages began.
And we give you the praise that on one
level or another, you have brought us
nearer to you. You have brought us into
this agenda of yours. And so we ask
again, send your word to us this
afternoon.
Help us to hear your voice.
Enlighten the eyes of our understanding.
Help us to understand the concepts
you're trying to communicate to us. And
let not one person leave here the same
way they came. Whether they are
physically in the room with us or they
are connected online. We give you the
praise. We give you the glory.
And the church of God shouted a loud
amen.
>> Oh hallelujah.
>> Just before you take your seat, can we
celebrate um which is not calling you
pastor now? Apostle E.
Please let's celebrate our youth church
leader
and all the other ministers in the
house.
Mrs. Yu, you're welcome.
I know there were some other people that
ministered earlier. We are grateful to
God for what he's doing. Praise the
Lord. Then let me turn to a neighbor to
your left and to your right and tell
them I celebrate you.
You too, you are awesome.
You are immaculately beautiful.
You are glorious.
And God is taking you somewhere.
Let's be seated. God bless you.
We have very limited time and I will try
to work with the time I have. So, and I
will just um add a thing or two to the
things we have been hearing at this
conference. Has somebody been blessed so
far?
Again, about half of us. Let me try
again. Has somebody been blessed so far?
Praise the Lord.
I think in a youth conference like this
is good to tell everyone and remind
everyone please try and pay attention
some of you are bowing down I don't know
whether it's your phones you are
watching
if your neighbor is playing with your
phone please help me elbow them pay
attention pay attention
and it's important for me that those of
you that are backing I think the way
they sit around if you can turn your
seats so turn your seats so we can have
face to face contact. Yeah, this time
for the word. Don't let your phone
distract you. Please pay attention. Um
me, I won't even allow you know. So, let
me lay that one.
Like I always tell people, um cuz
typically I visit church after church.
Now, I'm not resident pastor in any
church. So, I always warn people in
advance in case I say something that you
don't like, don't worry. your pastor
will come and massage you after I've
gone. I will only promise you that I
will do my best to say the truth. Praise
the Lord. So please let's pay attention
just a few minutes. Don't allow that
brother is still not paying attention.
You don't sleep in church. Whether you
are young or old, don't put down your
head. So pay attention. Praise the Lord.
It's good for you to realize that you
are not too young to hear the word of
God.
not too young.
Um, perhaps the youngest example we have
in scriptures is John the Baptist.
And the Bible said when Mary came to
visit Elizabeth,
I mean Jesus was not even born,
it was the greeting of Mary, the voice
of the mother. That's the voice of the
mother of Christ when he was in the womb
and he responded to the word of God. The
Bible said the baby in Elizabeth's womb
lipped when she heard the voice of Mary
because Mary too was pregnant.
I mean that that's just remarkable.
And then we can go on and on. Samuel was
another very good example. He had just
been weaned. The Bible didn't give us a
specific age when his mother brought him
to the temple. So I I've actually not
done the research. I think I I will
check it again. But he couldn't have
been up to five years old.
And God now bypassed the prophet. Eli
was the prophet in those days, but God
had sacked him.
And God wanted to raise another
generation.
And this child that the mother dedicated
to God was the person God was now
speaking to. And it was so bad in those
days that Eli will now be hearing from
Samuel because he knew that is Samuel
God is now talking to. What did God tell
you? That's how he was now hearing from
God.
So let me tell someone, you're not too
young to hear.
Not too young. And the earlier you know
that the better.
The Bible told us about Jesus at the age
of 12. Most of you here are older than
12. At the age of 12,
he was already in the temple like we are
today discussing with the teachers and
the prophets.
And he was there for 3 days.
The parents were looking for him all
over. They went to nightclub. They
didn't see him there. Well, maybe not
nightclub.
They went to where do where do young
people go to? H mall. They didn't see
him in the mall. They went to the beach.
They didn't see him. And I love what he
told them when they found him and they
were like, "Ah, why did he do that? Why
did he leave them?" And he said that,
"Did you not know that I will be about
my father's business?"
In other words, okay, even if I I I
misled you and I went, the first place
you should have come to look for me was
in church.
If you had come to look, I'm not the
problem here. You are the one that mis
road.
If you had come to look for me where I
will be about my father, you would have
found me. So I wasn't the one that was
lost. You are the one that didn't know
the kind of son you had.
Somebody say I'm not too young.
And I tell you, the earlier the better.
The earlier you grasp these things. We
are talking about God has a plan for
your life. God has a purpose for your
life. You are not here by accident.
to the glory of God. We too started
hearing these things when we were your
age. I mean I I came into the word of
faith. I got born again. In fact, I was
even late relatively speaking. Early
20s, 1993. Yeah. 20 early 1920.
And fortunately for me, I started
hearing the word of God directly. I
didn't have any. My first Bible teacher
really that taught me the word was the
late Dr. Fred Casey Price. So I think I
had a very very good Bible teacher. It
was on TV. I I didn't go to Cshaw
Christian Center. It was but a weekly
diet LTV8 in those days if I remember
correctly. That was the first person I
saw open the word of God to me.
So I I think I had a very good word of
faith foundation.
And then not long after that I met Dr. K
and King's word. And what that encounter
did for me was what I was seeing an
American preacher preach on TV and I met
young Nigerian people. That that was
what fascinated me about King's word. Uh
these people are praying in the spirit
living doing the word like
and this was rather rare in those days
because in my parents church they didn't
even preach salvation in those days. Now
Orthodox churches preach new birth. In
those days there were I had never heard
of new birth. I had never heard of
speaking in tongues and I was in I grew
up in my parents church but those things
were we in those days we are talking 33
years ago now
I look back now
and some of my age mates that either did
not hear this thing because you can you
can be on this earth and you not hear
these things. Jesus told disciples,
"Blessed are your ears that you are
hearing these things. Blessed are your
eyes that you are seeing these things."
That there were people that came before
you that wanted to hear these things,
but it was not their time.
In fact, there were those that sought
God, prophets, but it wasn't yet their
time. Can somebody say, "My eyes are
blessed.
>> My ears are blessed."
I look back now 30 plus years later
those that did not hear my age mates now
we are in our mid-50s or thereabout now
or those that had and ran away from it I
mean I knew family and friends that I
tried to bring in some responded some
did not respond
listen to me I do not kid you not our
lives are
night and day
night and day it's just a worldart
There's nothing like the word of God
or the purpose of God for your life or
the plan of God for your life.
Praise the Lord.
Can you help me find that text? One
generation shall serve him onto another.
So let's quickly get into the time we
have because what God does now is
generation after generation.
And in Bible palance, look at scripture.
For God a generation is roughly 20
years.
20 years. That that's how God counts
generation. And we we can take that in
the story of the children of Israel.
It's in the book of Psalms. One
generation I I just that scripture just
came to my heart. I want to start from
there. Um when God brought out the
children of Israel from Egypt
and that generation decided not to
believe him to enter the promised land.
This was the verdict of God. Everybody
that is up to 20 years,
you are not going to enter the promised
land. That was the cut off point. In
other words, by the age of 20, God
expects you to start taking
responsibility for your life. You can't
say it's my parents anymore.
You can't say it's my pastor anymore.
Even if your pastor was teaching you
rubbish, you should have read the Bible
enough by yourself.
You can't blame somebody else.
Praise the Lord.
Look at this. One generation shall
praise your works to another and shall
declare your mighty acts.
So if if God is still going by that 20
year, maybe God is even using 10 years
these days because things are
accelerating. We don't know. Oh 15
years.
It's important to know that in your
generation, somebody say in my
generation,
God wants us to praise his works that to
announce his works to serve him.
Hallelujah.
And to declare his mighty acts.
Several years ago, I was praying. I was
looking at some of our fathers in the
faith, Baba Deui and Bishop
particularly those two came to my mind
and I was like how can we ever match up
with these people I mean the the gap was
just to
and then God gave me another perspective
I love what pastor said sometimes that's
what God does for his perspective when
you when you walk with God and you live
the life of faith is God just shifts
your perspective and this was what God
told me that day because I was like what
more can we do we can I don't think we
are going to catch up to these people or
do more than them and God said with
everything that they have done and
preached how many people are born again
how many people are saved look at your
country look at your world your world is
still upside down that tells you that
there's still more work to be done
so we celebrate what the fathers before
us have done we learn from them but if
this world is still upside down the way
it is if there's still poverty if there
are still sick people if they still
confused people. If they are still
depressed people,
God still needs a generation that will
declare.
Hallelujah.
And what I came to do this afternoon is
to tell somebody here, you are that
generation God is looking. You are the
one. Somebody say, I'm the one. If
you're not talking, you're a suspect.
Let me hear you. Let me feel you. Say, I
am the one.
You need to start accepting that God
wants to pioneer new frontiers of the
gospel through your life.
Let me let's stay with scriptures that
most of us are probably familiar with,
particularly those of us that come to
church regularly. God wants to do
something. 1 Corinthians chapter 2:9,
eye has not seen, ear has not heard,
has not entered the hearts of men the
things God has prepared.
So we still have light problem in
Nigeria with all the preaching and
anointing that we have done. Maybe is
you on your generation that God is going
to use one of you. Nigeria has not won
World Cup. We didn't even go. We've not
gone for work up the last two world cup.
A nation like ours, Kate Vad has entered
round two,
they soon they will soon catch up with
our record.
You know, when we are talking about God,
we are talking about all facets of life.
We not just talking about church. If we
keep God in church, we have failed. In
fact, that was the failure of
generations before us. It was
particularly when we started growing up
in the faith that God now started
revealing to us that God is not for
church only.
We started hearing messages about the
seven mountains of God that God wants to
dominate everywhere.
The same thing he said from the very
beginning Genesis 1 verse 28 from verse
26. Go to verse 28 because of time. Let
us make man in our image and after our
likeness. In fact go to verse 26. Let's
start from there. Put your name in that
man. You see you have to learn to read
the Bible to understand that it's a love
letter from God to you. So before you
think it's just general man. No. When I
read this text, I say, "Let us make
pastor tea."
I want to understand that I'm the one
God is talking to.
>> And the earlier you c that, the better.
When Jesus was going to start his
ministry, the Bible said he came to the
temple. You see, you read this story in
Luke chapter 4. Stay here because of
time. And he opened to Isaiah chapter
60. And he read, the text did not put
his name there. The text read, "The
spirit of the Lord is upon me." But
Jesus believed and he knew that I am the
me in that text. Somebody say I am the
man in this text.
>> And then he told them today is this
scripture fulfilled in your hearing.
That's what it means when he says one
generation shall serve him. You see what
God has prophesied. I was following the
conference when he started and I saw
Dickin reading from Isaiah 60. Arise,
shine. And you tell yourself, I'm the
one God is telling to arise. I am the
one God is telling to shine. It is in my
generation, my lifetime, that God will
fulfill what he has said, the one that
has not yet been fulfilled. And there
are many things that have not been
fulfilled.
Thank God for all that has been done by
the fathers, but there are still many
things that have not been fulfilled.
Partly because it was not yet their
time.
Esther's uncle told Modiah, he told her,
"You don't know whether you have been
you have brought it, you have been
coming to for such a time as this.
There are certain things they are for
now. They for your generation."
Hallelujah.
So he said, "Let us make pastor T,"
somebody put your name there again in
our image and likeness. Verse 27 before
the ladies start saying that I'm not
included though he made them who and how
how how did he make us
you can't hide sir
you know there are some customs and
religions and it sometimes creeps into
some do denominations that women cannot
serve God you will never find it in the
Bible
male and female
he made them
Every gender has its purpose.
And you read verse 28, the the
assignment was let them have dominion
over the earth. We are not seeing people
of God having dominion over the earth.
Not to the degree we should. And there
is that generation of the children of
God that they will have dominion over
the earth. It has happened before and it
will happen again. Joseph had dominion
over the earth. David had dominion over
the earth. Moses had dominated. They
dominated the world. When they mention
their name, the US president feared. US
president is the one having dominion.
Hallelujah.
So we need to start believing these
things.
quickly where I want to go today.
Matthew chapter 1 verse one. As I begin
to close, can somebody say, "It is my
time."
It is our time.
Hallelujah.
If you're not talking, it's either you
don't believe me or you have not yet
summoned up the courage. You see, there
are two things here. There are people
that will not believe these things.
Sadly,
it's like that generation of the
wilderness church and their own case was
actually very sad and pathetic because
it wasn't that they were not people of
faith. They were people of faith.
Hebrews chapter 11, I think it's verse
29 told us that it was by faith that
they crossed the Red Sea.
Look at it. Hebrews 11:29. By faith they
believed God. They they had to believe
God and they had to believe by faith.
They passed through the Red Sea.
So they were people of faith. But that
you use faith to pass the Red Sea
doesn't mean you will have faith to
enter the promised land.
That you had faith in January doesn't
mean you have faith in June.
>> See faith is a present continuous virtue
that you must. It's like breathing. That
you breathe yesterday does not mean you
are not going to breathe today. You have
to be breathing every moment or else.
So these people they walk they they had
seen faith at and that's why God was
angry with them
when they took the communion. That's
what we call it today
when God told them to slaughter the lamb
and put the blood on the lintil and to
eat it which was the type of the blood
of Jesus in Exodus chapter 12 and
chapter 13 when God was going to bring
the final verdict on Egypt. They did it
by faith.
Because how does faith work? God gives
you an instruction.
God told Moses, "I'm going to bring the
final judgment on Egypt. I'm going to
kill the firstborn of everybody in the
land. Tell the children of Israel they
should slaughter." He gave them the
instructions. They could have said, "I'm
not going to do that. How does killing
Uhhuh. is it not the same suya we ate
yesterday? How does eating suya protect
me and my household? I'm not going to."
But all of them believed it and all of
them did it. And when the angel of death
came, he passed over them. I prophesy
over somebody under the sound of my
voice. Sickness will pass over you.
Poverty passes over you. Premature death
will pass over you.
God will satisfy you with long life. You
will not die before your time.
>> Hallelujah. Please be seated. They were
there there were people that were not um
it's not that they didn't know anything
about faith
but this time now came in Exodus chapter
13 and Exodus chapter 14 after the spies
went to promise the land they now said
I'm not going to believe
God told them go into the promised land
I we I know they are giants yeah we go
ahead of we kill these giants
said except for Joshua and Caleb they
refused to believe
and I'm telling you That spirit of
unbelief can be at work. It will not be
our portion in Jesus name.
>> See this what Hebrews chapter 4 was
teaching us that there should not be an
evil heart of unbelief in any of us that
what God is saying today. Hebrews
chapter 3:7.
So you have you you you
have to believe these things because
it's the word of God. Hebrews 3:7 the
Bible says that we should not allow a
today. Today in 2026, what's today's
date? 27th.
That you believe it yesterday doesn't
mean you are believing it today.
It's possible that in January you
believe that God could use you to change
the world, but now June, maybe you went
through a difficult first half of the
year. You're now doubting it. See, the
operative word is today. As the Holy
Spirit says today,
if you hear his voice, do not harden
your heart. Next verse. This is my
prayer that as as I share these things
with you,
somebody will not harden their hearts.
Cuz I'm telling you from my own little
life and my own personal experience,
when they were telling us these things
30 something years ago, some of my age
mates harden their hearts. We are not on
the same level today, sir.
You're not on the same level.
There's just something wrong when you
refuse to believe the word of God. In
fact, he calls it an evil heart. Do not
harden your heart as in the re. He calls
it rebellion.
In the day of trial in the wilderness,
go to chapter 4 quickly. Verse 7.
Chapter 4:7.
Chapter 4. I mean, if you've never
studied Hebrews chapter 3 and Hebrews
chapter 4, I hope you know you're not
too young to read the Bible. Talk to me,
church.
>> And you are not too young to study the
Bible.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Please go and study it.
Look at this. Um.
Aha. Verse eight. Give me verse 8.
Give me verse 9.
There rem
11. I want to where where he said an
evil out of unbelief. Let us therefore
be diligent to enter that rest. Lest any
fall according to the same example of
disobedience. Verse 12
verse 13. That that place of evil out of
unbelief. Ah I think you've passed it.
Go back to verse five. Let's start from
verse five. I said verse seven. Uh verse
6. Let me see.
Aha. No. This is not the one I'm looking
for. Go back a bit. Please permit me.
Verse verse two or three. I'm No, no,
no. Up, up, up. Give me that verse.
Start from verse three. Let's see verse
three. He calls it an evil house. They
not enter the rest of my ro. They shall
not enter my rest. Verse four. Give me
verse four.
Ah, I'm wasting too much time on this.
If you study, he said that we should not
allow an evil heart of unbelief.
And what he was talking about, there
were people that God told them, "This is
my agenda for you. This is what I want
to do.
I want to take you into the promised
land. I I want to use you to you to
spread my glory all over the earth. They
now refuse to be Is it in chapter 3?
Okay, go back to chap chapter if you can
find the verse for me. Chapter 3 verse
what? Verse 12 in chapter 3. Sorry.
Please go back there. Yeah. Beware,
brethren, lest there be in any of you
an evil heart of unbelief in departing
from the living God.
Please follow me. Follow me. If your
neighbor is not heads up, I'm seeing
some people bing. Help me elbow them. Be
your brother's keeper today. Don't
worry. I will soon be gone. I have just
a few minutes to go. Don't Don't let let
them hear. So it's not just that they
did not hear because some people can I
didn't know. No, you know. But we play
this video for you in heaven.
You know,
and there's a genuine case that some
people will never hear this kind of
gospel. That's what he called it in
verse two of chapter 4. He said they did
not mix faith with the gospel. So, he
did not profit them.
One young person in Gaza may have an
excuse to say, "I didn't hear that God
wanted to use me in my generation. All
my life I was fighting bombs from
Israeli government.
I had more important things to attend
to. Bomb you. Yeah, there's no bump sir.
You are sitting in an AC auditorium.
The youth pastor has preached. Other
pastors has preached. The DP has come to
preach. Sir, let me tell anybody, you
have no excuse.
You have no excuse.
I always tell people, you have entered
holy one chance.
You can't escape.
Just in case you are thinking why did I
even come for this meeting [laughter]
I've entered only one chance. Well don't
worry it's for it's good for your
destiny
you must or we must hear these things
and then we must believe them. That
that's where the journey start that in
fact that's a major part of what God
wants you to do to believe.
Matthew chapter 1 vers1 as I begin to
close. I I love the way the New
Testament started.
Do you know the Bible, the whole of the
Bible is all about Jesus?
Please follow me. I'm I'm I'm I'm
closing.
It's all about Jesus. Bible said when
Jesus resurrected
after he died, two of the disciples were
walking on the road to Emmas
and they were discussing about the death
of Jesus. And Jesus came beside them and
he now started berating them that why
are you talking in a negative light? Did
you not know that the Christ was
supposed to come and die? And the Bible
said he began from Moses. Moses is the
first five books of the Bible. Genesis.
Genesis. And he began to reveal to them
things pertaining himself. And that's
what the Bible this scripture is telling
us here. The book of the genealogy of
Jesus Christ. The whole of the Bible is
about Jesus Christ.
But this where it gets interesting here.
He now said the son of David. Ah
David was not the father of Jesus
biologically speaking. And then he now
said the son of Abraham. Ah Abraham was
not the biological father of David.
So of all the men and that's what
Matthew chapter 1 was doing here from
verse two. Give us verse two to all the
way to verse 17. They now gave us the
record of from Abraham
all the way to Jesus. And you see
Abraham did not begget David. He begat
Isaac and they start listing it until
they got to Joseph the biological father
of Jesus in verse 17. But look at the
way verse one was constructed. Please
follow me. Follow me. Follow me.
It's all about Jesus.
And Jesus is the son of David. It's
a mystery. You know Jesus asked them one
day he was teaching. He said
um why is the Christ called the son of
David?
Because David himself said the Lord said
to my Lord God the father. See the the
the Hebrew and the Jewish people knew
the text. The father said to
the son, "Sit at my right hand
till I make your enemies my fto." The
Lord said to my Lord. So Jesus answer,
why if if David was his father? If Jesus
because it's a prophetic name and it's a
mystery prophetic name. If if Jesus was
if the Christ was the son of David, how
could David call him Lord? Nobody had an
answer. And I don't think we still have
the answer today other than it's a
mystery. It's one of the mysteries of
God.
But what was he trying to tell us here?
Keep my text up. Matthew 1:1. No, still
on Matthew 1:1. The genealogology.
So of all those men that they gave us
from verses 2 to verse 17, David stood
out.
And before David, Abraham stood out.
So we read scriptures like we should
follow after the faith of Abraham
and that we should embrace the spirit of
David. We find those two.
But more importantly, please please as I
close this this this is a major piece of
what you must grasp today. It's
important to understand understand that
David was not just a human being
or a personality or a character. He was
a concept. Abraham
was not just a human being. Please
follow me. I'm going to break it down
for you. Don't miss this. He was a
concept.
See, God was revealing himself
in Christ to man.
And he was trying to tell us concepts
about God.
And what stood Abraham out in his
generation?
What stood Abraham out was that when God
shared the idea of Abraham with Abraham,
the concept of Abraham. What's the
concept of Abraham? That what's the
story of Abraham? We we were introduced
to Abraham in Genesis chapter 12
from verse one. Please go there. And the
Bible said, "Now the Lord had said to
Abraham,
God is looking for a man he can say
something to that will believe him
even though his situation and
circumstances don't look like it."
God told him, "I will make you great. I
will make you a great nation. I will
bless you. Go on with me. And through
you all the families of the earth will
be blessed." Verse verse three.
God told a man something ridiculous and
outrageous like he's going to tell you
and I ridiculous and outrageous things.
I'm sure some of you are finding it
ridiculous that God wants to use in your
generation. Yes, that's how Abraham felt
in Genesis 12.
And verse 4 tells us something.
At this time Abraham was not even a
young man. He was a 75year-old barren
man.
Isaiah 51 said he was alone. I was
studying that text one day. The Holy
Ghost told me he was broke. He was a
broke. He didn't have any wealth. It was
in chapter 13 that he became wealthy
after God had spoken to him. He didn't
have any money. He didn't have any
children. And in those Bible days to be
without children, the shame.
He had nothing, no air.
But he had something which God is
looking for in this generation. They
call it faith.
someone that would dare to believe God
even if what God is saying doesn't make
sense and I'm telling you God is going
to tell you things that don't make sense
we are sitting in King's world today the
day God spoke to our father Dr. K he was
a teenager like most of you raised me a
supernatural army it didn't make sense
when God showed him I'm going to take
you I'm going to use you to take my
gospel to the nations it didn't make
sense Dr. Okay, we say I didn't have a
passport. I had never seen a plane
concept.
Who will believe me when I tell them I
want to do great things in their lives?
And this is it. This if if verse four
did not happen, we will not be
discussing Abraham today.
And Abraham was 75 years old. And he
departed from Harang. He responded to
what God told him. Can somebody shout,
"By grace, I will respond to the word of
God."
That's the concept we are trying to
teach here. It's a concept.
Chapters 1 to chapter 11 of Genesis,
THEY WERE TALKING ABOUT ALL OTHER men
from Adam that did not do what God
eventually found Abraham doing. Starting
from Adam, look, go back to that Matthew
chapter 1 verse one. Let me rewrite that
text for you. Let me rewrite it for you
in the original way. It ought to have
been the genealogy of Jesus, THE SON OF
SAUL. THE FIRST KING GOD PICKED was
Saul.
>> But he didn't understand the concept
that God was trying to bring out through
his life. The first man God created
wasn't Abraham. Oh, it was Adam.
>> That that's how this text should have
been.
But sadly some people will not believe
God when God speaks to them. Somebody
say I reject it in Jesus name.
It will not be my portion in Jesus name.
These concepts are just too big for
certain people
and you have nothing to lose. God is
saying I will is what I want to do in
your life. Let's even say God
disappoints and God has never
disappointed and he doesn't do it. You
have not lost anything.
You are the way you were before God
spoke to you. [laughter] You have not
lost anything.
Faith doesn't cost you anything.
What's the concept of David? When you
study 1 Samuel chapter 13
the day God sacked King Saul,
there were two sack letters King Saul
got in 1 Samuel chapter 13 and then in 1
Samuel chapter 15.
studying the story behind it is very
very powerful. But let's leave that for
now. This was what Samuel told Saul
and if you read it because of time we
won't go there. I need to quickly get to
something and I can I can close. My time
has just give me 5 10 minutes I will
close.
Praise the Lord.
What was Saul's problem? S told him you
did not obey the word of God. You didn't
obey what God told you. Said now the
kingdom will be taken from you. And this
is what he said in that first s chapter
13. Um he said God
has given the kingdom to a man after my
heart. His heart.
Now watch watch. We had not been
introduced to David yet. We were
introduced to David in chapter 16. As at
the time Samuel was saying that to King
Saul, he never knew David existed.
Perhaps God knew. Well, God must have
known.
But this is my point. I don't think God
had actually picked David at that time.
Please just follow my train of thought.
I don't think so. This was just the job
description. It's a concept. The the
person I want to use is like Zenith Bank
is looking for their new MD. So they not
going to hire a carpenter. They will
look for somebody that went to Harvard
or wherever he has a masters in this.
This is the JD. This is the the person
that fits the profile. In the case of
God, I need a man after my heart.
Then God says, "Scan
and then sometime before chapter 16, God
found David." The the job description
was clear. The problem with Saul was
that he wasn't after God's heart. Other
things matter to him more than God.
So God found Abraham someone that will
believe me against all odds. Can
somebody say, "Find me, Lord. Find me,
Lord." And then God found David, someone
that will, my heart is after God.
So when he tells us, go back to my
Matthew 1:1,
the genealogy of Jesus, I want to tell
someone in 2026
in these last days we are living in the
young people God is looking for, they
feel they fit the profile of David
and they fit the profile of Abraham.
Am I making sense to you?
Help me elbow your neighbor to your left
and to your right. Particularly if your
neighbor is looking at a phone, say,
"Pay attention." No, pay attention. Tell
them, "I know you're a young person, but
pay attention. Pay attention.
Help them. Help them." Cuz some someone
is already scanning his phone again.
Verse 18 is where I want to close with.
So after they told us this is the
profile and they give us the list of
everybody. The Bible now came to Mary.
See Mary fits the profile.
Who was Mary? She was a teenage girl.
See there was a prophecy. Isaiah chapter
7 captures it.
God said I will show you a sign. Can you
raise your hand and say, "My life is a
sign and a wonder
>> in my generation."
>> In my generation,
>> God said, "I will show you a sign. A
virgin will conceive."
Isaiah was hundreds of years before Mary
was born, perhaps even thousands.
And this young girl was now going to be
the person, the first person in this
case, God didn't have to find a
replacement for Mary. There are some
people God didn't have to find a
replacement for because when God told
them what they wanted to do, they
believed him. God didn't have to find a
replacement for Joseph.
God didn't have to find a replacement
for Mary. God did not have to find a
replacement for Apostle Paul.
Can I share something with you? When we
get to heaven, we will find out.
I think Apostle Paul replaced Apostle
Peter
in my reading of the book of Acts
cuz I see the narrative in the book of
Acts from Acts chapter 9 to Acts chapter
1 to Acts chapter 9 or even chapter 10.
The story was it was this the story was
being told from the lens of the ministry
of Apostle Peter and it was in Acts
chapter 10 God revealed to Peter that
this thing is not just for the Jews
I'm starting with the Jews but it's for
the ends of the earth when God took him
to the house of Cornelius and the Bible
say while Peter was preaching and God
showed him the urgency God did not even
allow him to finish his message the Holy
Ghost fell and then the Gentiles are
speaking in tongues. And Peter
understood what God was saying with all
the encounters God had with him. But
Peter did not want to leave the Jews.
God now found one radical. I pray for
somebody. God will not replace you.
>> God will not replace you. Sir and Paul
was a murderer. A murderer. In fact, he
was on a
assassination mission when God found
him. May God not use murderer to replace
you. Do
>> you know some of the ridiculous people
God use lots may God not use lot to
replace you
>> Jacob was a 419 s me they not use 419
>> he was going to attack the church and
kill he had killed Steven he was now
going to Damascus
but he just recognized Jesus
they came to tell this teenage age girl.
Luke chapter 1, I think start from
around verse 32. Blessed art thou among
women. You know that prophecy in Isaiah
that a virgin will conceive. You are
that virgin.
>> And she believed it.
Sir, what are you believing?
They came to meet David. God is going to
replace King Saul. You are the king.
David was a shepherd boy and he believed
it.
>> They came to tell Esther they have
sacked the queen. She was a foreigner.
Orphan girl foreigner. You are the one
that's going to be. And she believed it.
One generation
shall praise his name onto the next.
Let me close by telling you this. God is
going to raise people like David in your
day. He will raise Abraham's in your
day. He will raise Joseph's in your day.
Joseph saw a dream. The whole world was
bowing down to me. Everybody whoever who
they who them be I am the man. He didn't
understand the dream but he believed it.
>> Imprisonment did not shake it out of
him.
>> Slavery did not shake it out of him.
How can they tell you that you will give
birth to God without knowing a man
>> and you believe it? She didn't need one
year. It's not that she came for youth
conference. She didn't need a youth
conference. All this they talk to me
there are many things people are doing
that for me it's too much. I've said I'm
not going to be talking much again.
Honestly
I've learned I'm I'm undergoing that
transformation phase. This this media
season is one of the recalibration. I'm
not
I'm talking too much.
It's not that Mary woke up one morning
and they had trick to her that no and
she didn't have to come for a youth
conference.
you have to come for a youth conference.
She only has one question. How will it
happen?
>> And she asked it with the right attitude
because if you check the story very
well, it's the same question. There's
nothing wrong with asking those kind of
questions. If you don't ask ask it in
the like Zechariah because they have the
same question. See sometimes not what
you are saying that problem. It's your
attitude. This man is smiling at me but
God can see his attitude.
I think he's my friend. How is married
life?
>> I've not seen him since he got married.
His attitude. Zechariah has the same
question.
I'm the angel of I came to tell you good
news. Said you will not talk until this
mission is finished.
>> Praise the Lord.
>> Listen,
God wants to use you. That's
like he used Mary.
And I I like Mary's story because this
Matthew give us that verse 18. Our own
assignment wasn't to preach. Our
assignment wasn't to plant church. Our
assignment wasn't to raise the dead. Our
assignment was to just present her body
to God. For God to impregnate her and
for her to carry the pregnancy to full
time and to nurture the baby. That was
the only job God gave her.
May you find your assignment in life and
may you find it early
>> and may you fulfill it
within the grand scheme of God.
>> So our assignment was just to be the
mother of God and on the day of
Pentecost in Acts chapter 1 she was
still in the church not that okay I'm a
mother and I have no business with
church.
Yes. My own assignment is not preaching.
My own assignment, my own assignment is
just to give birth to God. But I'm still
a part of the church. He was there on
the day.
Hallelujah.
Rise on your feet this afternoon.
Lift your hands to heaven and say, "God,
come on. Let me hear you. Say, God,
>> now that I know, I know you want to use
me. I ask for mercy. I ask for mercy. I
ask for grace. Use me Lord in the name
of Jesus. Can you open your mouth and
turn into prayer?
[music]
Come on, pray studio. Find this text for
me in Acts chapter 13. David after he
had served his generation, slept with
his fathers. I I think it's verse I
can't remember the verse. Acts chapter
13 or thereabouts. David after he had
served his generation. Kamakosa.
Come on, somebody from the depth of your
heart. Pray it like Mary prayed it with
the right attitude. Use me Lord.
Use me Lord. Use me. Use me Lord.
Pray it like Mary prayed it with the
right attitude. I [music] may not be
perfect.
I may not know everything.
I may not know my left hand from my
right hand. But Lord, now that I've had
this thing [music]
that you want to use me in my lifetime,
in my generation, use me, Lord. Use me,
Lord. Use me for the purpose for which
you made me. Use me. Use me. [music]
Can I give you one more minute to pray?
Pray that prayer [music] sincerely.
Pray that prayer sincerely.
>> [music]
>> We'll come back to this verse 36. Go to
Luke 1:37. Keep praying, church. Keep
praying. Luke chapter 1:37.
Luke 1:37. quickly.
34 34
in the name of Jesus.
Look at what Mary asked there. He said
how how is it going to happen when the
vision or the plan of God for our life
what God wanted to pioneer through our
life
and in our own case it's a very very
unique assignment because it has never
happened before and it will never happen
again.
>> There are some things God uses you to
break through then other people can
start doing it. This one there won't be
a replica. God is not coming back in the
form of flesh again.
It's important to first accept the fact
that she believed it. As ridiculous as
it sounded,
you're going to get pregnant without
knowing a man. As ridiculous as it
sounded, and it's not just any pregnancy
you're going to be pregnant, you're
going to give birth to the Christ. And
then um next verse Gabriel told her and
this is the prayer I want you to pray.
The Holy Ghost will come upon you. The
power of the highest will overshadow
you. Again, attitude though. Attitude is
everything. Raise your hand. Say, "Holy
Spirit, come on. Let me hear you. Let me
feel you." Say, "Holy Spirit, come upon
me. Aresh power of the highest
overshadow me like never before in the
name of Jesus." Come on, turn into
prayer for a minute.
[music]
Holy Spirit, come upon me. Come upon me.
Aresh [music] power of the highest,
cover me, overshadow me, envelope me.
Not just for this hour, but always and
forever. Come upon me aresh. Overshadow
me. Come upon me Aresh. Overshadow me.
Come upon me Aresh.
Acts 13:36. [music]
Somebody keep praying. Ask that prayer.
Pray that prayer. Acts 13:36.
Acts 13:36.
A somebody is still praying for David
after he had served his generation by
the will of God.
Somebody declare this afternoon. I
receive grace. Say it out loud. I
receive grace to serve my generation by
the will of God. One more time. I
receive grace. I receive mercy. I
receive help from above to serve my
generation in the name of Jesus. to
serve my generation by the will of God
in the name of Jesus. Open your [music]
mouth, raise your voice, pray.
[music]
Oh,
GRACE
[music]
TO SERVE
MY GENERATION.
KA.
[music]
No shadow you won't light up.
Mountain you won't climb up. Coming
after me.
No [music] wall you won't kick down. Lie
you won't tear down. Coming after me.
[music and singing]
>> No shadow you won't light up. Mountain
you won't climb up. [music]
coming after me. [singing]
>> No wall [music] you won't kick down. Lie
you won't tear down. Coming after me.
No shadow you won't light [music] up.
Mountain you won't climb up. Coming
after [singing] me.
>> No wall
you won't stand up. Sing it again and
again. No shadow
mountain you won't climb. Coming after.
>> Raise your voice. I declare it. No
shadow.
>> He won't shadow. [music]
coming after me. [music]
>> Coming after
>> coming after [screaming] me. No.
>> One more time.
There's no shadow. [screaming]
coming after me. [music]
>> [music]
>> and all the overwhelming
[music]
ever
[singing]
changes
might [music]
be the
>> [singing]
>> I
don't
I don't deserve [music]
it. You give yourself
and
[music]
[singing]
>> one more time. SOMEBODY believes this.
I will be never restless. [music]
Oh, he changes. [music]
>> I couldn't
but I don't deserve it till you gave
yourself away.
Oh, the [singing] overwhelming
[music]
never ending
reckless love of God. [singing]
>> No shadow you won't light up, mountain
you [music] won't climb up.
>> Coming after me.
>> I hope somebody understands.
>> God came after us
>> and he's still coming after us today.
Several years ago, God gave me a vision.
>> Do you know there is a young man, a
young woman in India,
he may even have graduated from
Microsoft School of Engineering and he
can write the latest AI code,
but he's going to one shrine
after he leaves his office.
I used to work with Microsoft in those
days. I was consulting some work for
them
and uh God was telling me that if not
that
those missionaries from Europe and
America came to Africa to preach the
gospel to our forefathers and by the
grace of God some of our forefathers
accepted it. You will be in a shrine
today
like your age mate in India is probably
still carrying
technologically gifted. You may even be
able to build a car. You know India is
ahead of us in technology. But they are
still idol worshippers. See this thing
is spiritual. Satan will accept that
deal with you any day. In fact build AI
go to mass
as long as your heart is not for Jesus.
He will give you the deal.
So I want us to understand and it should
not be lost to us. This is the love of
God that you are hearing these things
and that you can believe them and that
you can begin to act of them because
your age mates in other parts of the
world they are probably worshiping one
idol somewhere.
It's the love of God.
So don't take it for granted.
Don't take it for granted
that you have the privilege to believe
God. That that you have to know that God
exists.
There are still people today that don't
believe God.
And let me tell you something about the
devil. Even in Europe and America, the
people that brought the gospel to us,
some of their children are atheists now.
They don't believe God. Satan has
somehow Satan is not going to give up
that you're a believer. He can come
after your children or your children's
children.
They have all the money in the world,
but they don't know Jesus. And let me
tell you, the assignment upon us,
we are the ones that God is going to use
to save them. You didn't say amen
because when they came to preach the
gospel to us and God was granting our
forefathers grace, it could have been
the other way around. They could have
taken it to India.
And God would have granted their fore
parents grace to to believe. And they
are now the ones that now want to come
and save us in Africa. But God by his
election of grace, he chose us.
Chose us. Let's not take it for granted.
You don't have to understand everything.
Even me, I'm there are things I'm still
trying to understand.
But the one God grants you faith to
believe. Grab it. Give me Galatians 3:29
as we close. If you be Christ,
you are Abraham's seed
and you are the heir of this promise.
It was a promise God gave Abraham.
That's what God does.
I was teaching about using Dangote as an
example the other day. Said God is not
going to give you refinery. is crude oil
that we are going to give you. Then we
are going to give you brain that can
figure out how to translate crude oil to
petrol to kerosene
and we will help you to do it. But you
are the one that has to do it. So it
does promise they gave Abraham and he
said if you're in Christ you have the
same promise.
The way I've used Abraham to spread the
gospel to the ends of the earth. I want
to you are the L in 2026.
There are still many nations of the
world they don't know these things.
And from one generation to another
generation, God is looking for the
Abrahams that we believe today.
There's a second part of this message. I
don't have the time
cuz we are not talking about believe
because everything is okay. No, there
will still be obstacles. Some of you is
because of the obstacles before you.
That's why you're not running with this
thing. I don't have money. I don't have
a job. I don't have admission. I don't
All of them had all those obstacle
wants to chase you now to put you in
prison. Who is that guy they chasing? So
worry. Imagine if you
[laughter]
now I don't know whether they innocent
or guilty. That's not my point.
Don't let any obstacle disturb you.
There will always be obstacles and God
is going to use those obstacles to train
you
like Joseph.
Raise your hand and say, "In the name of
Jesus,
I lay hold and I take full delivery of
my inheritance
in Christ as Abraham's seed." Pray it
one more time. Say, by faith
>> I lay hold of my inheritance
in Christ as Abraham's seed in the name
of Jesus. Open your mouth and turn into
prayer.
As we are praying, if any one of us is
here, if you are not yet born again
or you are not sure whether you are born
again,
pray everyone pray. You see, you have to
be in Christ to have this thing. You
have to be in Christ. Or maybe you've
been born again before, but you are
backsliding and now you are not sure and
you you feel you need to rededicate your
heart or your life to Christ again, to
God again. As we are praying, quickly
come come and meet me here at the altar.
I will wait for a minute or two. Every
other person that can pray in the Holy
Ghost, pray in the Holy Ghost. But if
you are in this house this afternoon or
perhaps you are watching online, you are
not born again or you know you need to
rededicate your life to Jesus again.
Come on, welcome him into your hearts.
If you're in the hall, please come come.
[music]
I lay hold on my inheritance in Christ.
I lay hold. I lay hold. I lay hold.
I am aware I have an inheritance. I lay
hold and I take full delivery. I lay
hold. I lay hold. My life is not an
accident. God has a purpose for me.
There are things God wants to pioneer
in my life and through my life. And this
season I lay hold. Anybody coming? Is
there anyone that needs to get born
[music] again?
It's an inheritance in Christ. You have
to be in Christ
or you need to rededicate your life. I
will wait for just one more minute.
Keep praying. Keep praying. Keep
praying. One more minute.
No shadow.
No shadow. You won't light up
mountain. You won't climb up
[music] coming after me.
>> No, [music and singing]
you won't kick down.
You won't tear down [music] coming after
me.
There's no shadow,
>> no shadow
[singing and music] mountain you climb
up. Coming after me. No one
there [singing]
lie you down coming after me. [singing]
>> I couldn't earn it.
>> I don't deserve it.
>> Still [singing] you gave yourself away.
and all [singing] the overwhelming
neverending
[music] breathless.
>> Listen, as I dropped the mic, um that
was Dr. K that was calling. We had
wanted him to speak a word of blessing
over us, but he's on his way to Canada
now.
Give me Isaiah 51. Let me close with
that text.
The father over this house that started
perhaps when he was the age of many of
us or even younger
from nation to nation. He was in London,
UK last month doing this thing.
Yesterday he was preaching somewhere in
the US supernatural Canada. He's on his
way to Canada now. We wanted him to
actually speak a blessing and he will
speak. He has he has the youth in his
heart
because we understand in this house is
from one generation to the other. We are
not going to be here forever. Ah someone
p to us now people that preach to us. So
we do we have to
hallelujah.
I love this thing here. He said listen
to me you who follow after
righteousness. You who seek the Lord.
Look to the rock from which you are
healed and to the hole of the pit from
which you are dug. What was he talking
about? Look at verse two. said, "Look at
your parents." And he was talking about
spirituality. Look to Abraham
and look to Sarah.
I don't know how long you have been a
part of this house. So look to your look
to our father. Look to Dr.
He's in transit now. He's going he's
taking the gospel to another nation.
He's going to spend the weekend with
them in Canada. Next month he's going to
be with us in Nigeria.
Some of you that's the kind of destiny
God has for you.
That's the kind and this conference is
to wake you up.
Ephesians 5:14
thou that sleepst
wake up to wake you up.
Arise from the dead and Christ will give
you life. Wake up.
You are not too young.
Some of you your own is not going to be
preaching. You see your assignment can
be like Mary. You own his business.
God wants to use you to look you need to
find your they all kingdom assignment.
So even if it's just parenting Mary's
assignment was a parenting assignment
but it was a special parenting
assignment. The mother of Samuel Anna
parenting assignment
but there were people that had covenant
sense. I recognize that God wants to use
my life to change the world.
The world. The world. That's the message
God sent. The world.
You can be local, but you are meant to
have a global impact.
Doesn't matter where is that place that
no not where does come from
honey.
Europe today, America tomorrow, Canada,
Africa, Asia.
Some people are sent to men to preach,
some people is business, some people is
family, some people is government, some
people is sports.
Look at all these footballers in the
world cup that are celebrating Christ. I
still saw an article the Christians that
are making Jesus famous playing football
and somebody will see that and it will
inspire them.
Find your place. Oh, don't be like those
my age mates that I said they had these
things.
Cuz a time comes, it's too late.
Time comes, it's too late.
Glory be to God.
I release the grace of God upon you
to impact your generation.
to touch lives all around you with these
words you have heard to make a
difference in your world.
It it takes a degree of I call it make a
difference m do a dod it takes a degree
of madness to walk with God. It is
madness to believe that the Holy Ghost
will give you a child will pregnant you.
But it's not madness as in you have you
are crazy. is make a difference. Make a
difference.
It's make a difference mentality. That's
what Dr. K had when God told him that
you are going to take the gospel to the
nations of the world.
And he believed it.
May that grace rest upon your life.
May you walk in the fullness and the
overflow dimensions of it.
>> Thank God for the fathers. Thank God.
But there's still a lot of work to be
done.
The intention of God is for the next
generation to carry doublefold,
tenfold, 100fold, a thousandfold,
infinity fold of the anointing on their
fathers so that where their fathers
could not get to, they can get there.
May that be your testimony in the name
of Jesus.
You look at the story of Abraham, Isaac,
Jacob, and Joseph in the book of
Genesis. It was Joseph that fulfilled
that promise God gave Abraham that
through you, I would touch the end
families of the world. It was Joseph
that in his lifetime, Abraham did not
see it, but he believed the promise and
gave it to Jacob. I mean to Isaac. Isaac
did not see it. He gave it to J. Um,
Jacob. Jacob did not see it in his
lifetime. But Joseph stood
and a global famine came in his day and
he saved the entire world from hunger
in his lifetime.
There are promises God has given us
we've not seen yet. Many of you here
it's in your lifetime
you will be standing and living in it.
May that be your testimony in the name
of Jesus.
You are not here by accident. You're not
in this gathering by accident.
David was a shepherd boy. Shepherd boy.
That's Katar in case you don't know.
Esther was an orphan girl in a foreign
land. Daniel was a war refugee.
But what did they have? They believed
what God said. They just their
circumstances was irrelevant. the
situation they found themselves did not
deter them.
Raise your hand and say, "I believe the
word of the Lord."
As I've had it today,
my life will make a difference. God will
pioneer things that will transform the
world in my life and through my life
by his grace.
Raise those hands and say, "I receive
it. I receive it. I receive it. I
receive it. I receive it. Receive it
consciously. Receive it. Receive it by
faith. I receive it. I receive the
wisdom I need. I receive the revelation
I need. I receive the favor I need. I
receive the power I need. I receive the
understanding I need. My ears are open.
My eyes are open. My heart is sensitive.
Oh, if David could fulfill his destiny,
I can fulfill mine. If Abraham could, I
can fulfill mine. Today, today, today I
receive it
by the mercies of God and by the grace
of God.
Oh, thank you, Father.
These ones are for signs and wonders
from the Lord [snorts] of hosts who
dwells amongst us. You are blessed. You
are favored.
>> God will use you to transform your world
in the name of Jesus.
Somebody shout aloud hallelujah.
Please let me encourage you. Start
immediately. I I I shared something
powerful in the midweek service on
Wednesday.
I shared and I want to reiterate it
here. We are teaching about faith. You
see these things can only work by faith.
If we tell you these things, if you
don't believe them, could they work?
It's only for people that can believe
them. as ridiculous and as as outlandish
as they are, it takes faith. And I was
learning something from the World Cup.
Every nation in the World Cup, they are
they are champions. The the the finals
of the World Cup is a gathering of
champions. But they are different
levels. They are the Kadis in the World
Cup. They will never they not going to
win the World Cup. Not this year.
The only there's only one way Kvad can
win the World Cup. God will have to come
down.
God will leave all his serious duties
and come and play on the not it's not
just that God gave them presence he has
to come and play God has to come and
play for them they can't win but it
doesn't change the fact that they are
champions we know the people that are
going to win is either Argentina or
Brazil or France Japan may surprise us
there are less than 10 of them why
listen listen there are certain things
that are required to win at that level.
But that does not change that everybody
is a winner already. Everybody in that
competition, everybody in this room is a
winner.
>> You can start doing this at your cad
level.
You start at your level. You have
already made it inside the room. You may
not be the DPO. You may not be able to
preach. You may not be like Dr. K flying
from one nation to the other. But at
your level,
at least you can do a giddy with. Who
did Keb draw with? They drew again
yesterday. You can do again. I not go
you. I go.
[laughter]
The sad part is some people will hear
these things, they will not do anything
about it.
So though they are winners, they are not
acting like winners.
And that's the difference. Someone will
say ah me I'm not messy. So they can
come and pump me 10. No. No. We don't
have to pump you 10. No.
You can draw.
You will not win the World Cup. We know
you're not going to win the World Cup,
but at least you're in the room. Please
go out with some dignity. Oh, may let's
let's let let's let let's let let's let
let's let let's let it be respectable to
not that you are you don't know who you
are.
That's one lesson I'm taking from the
World Cup. Everybody in the World Cup is
already a champion. We may not carry the
couple, but we made it here. If you're a
child of God, you can do these things we
are talking about. Start at your level.
Start at your level. Okay? If you're
going to save the world, save your
neighbor at least. Save your brother.
Bring somebody to church next Sunday.
Start from somewhere. Then grow. And if
you have what it takes, maybe one day
you will win the World Cup. But that you
won't win the World Cup doesn't mean you
are not a champion. Not everybody is
going to be able to win the Since
they've been playing World Cup, only
eight nations have won it
for different reasons. So in our own
case, Nigeria, Nigeria has capacity, but
we are not serious. So we're not going
to win it. So that that's a story for
another day
cuz that's another thing. But some
people they can never because they don't
have I mean Kat I think they only
250,000 people in the country. When are
they going to win World Cup? Not that
they qualified is sufficient. So my
point is please do something with these
things you had. God bless you.
>> Somebody celebrate
Pastor T. We love you.
>> [music]
>> You're not saying like you say pastor we
love you.
>> Thank you so much sir. Um please can we
celebrate as he steps please let him
step back into the lounge before come on
we can do that. We can do that.
Come on now.
[cheering]
Wow.
What a conference.
May I never lose my song. May I never
lose my space. You are worthy of my
worship.
Worthy [music and singing] of my praise.
>> You know the while he was talking that
was all I just kept hearing. May I never
lose my space.
Pastor didn't give me another revelation
today. Imagine he was supposed to be the
uh Jesus the son of a a son of Saul but
because Saul
may I never lose my space.
>> May I never lose my space. You are
worthy of my worship.
Worthy [singing] of my praise.
Has it been a great time so far? If
you're believing, can you celebrate
Jesus?
Very quickly, can you celebrate Jesus?
Okay, so quick one. Um, we're closing.
Um,
how many of you have enjoyed this
conference so far?
Okay, so I mean like like I said
earlier, it cost things to do these
things. Are we together? Of course,
we're not saying you should come and pay
after. I mean, you have come and pay.
No, that's not what we're saying. But I
would like you to give. Can we display
the offering information? I want us to
give you know um the offering
information will be displayed on the
screen. If you want to do transfer, I
mean if it is cash you want to do um
please ushers can you um give out the
offering envelopes you know let's do
that very can you be on strings for me
get jokes
um that's the offering information on
the screen you want to give your
offering
then if you would like to I mean to the
glory of God thank God for this
conference and if you'd like to still be
a part of it I mean you can still give
towards it just tag hit um
pioneers conference. I'm talking about
aside the offering that you're giving
right. I mean if you want to give
specially to the conference I mean I
mean it takes a lot to have this kind of
meeting. I would have loved to do it
bigger than this but I mean thank God
for where we are. Amen. Amen.
>> Thank God for where we are and of course
we're going to get better and better. I
mean we trust God for more finances as
we grow so that we can I mean so that we
can pack this place the way we would
have loved to. Thank God for the
finances that came in but we trust God
that more can come in. All right. So
aside the offering if you would like to
give towards the conference you know you
can target u the pioneers conference so
that when we sit we know that it's a
special seed towards the conference. All
right is somebody ready to go home?
Is somebody ready to go home? Before you
go let me just make few announcement
just three to the glory of god our next
major meeting. Is somebody ready to hear
it? Rise up on your feet as we close. So
that you know we just announce it and we
close our next major meeting like this.
Of course in in Lagos we have been
having a lot of meetings but I mean
based on instruction
by the Holy Spirit and of course from my
at the top we're going to be doing a lot
of you know involving other
installations where these things are
concerned and you know I'll just reach
out to installation reps and you know I
will just discuss with them. All right.
But our next major meeting coming up
November last Saturday is tagged. Are
you ready? It's tagged Owen Bi after
party.
You're not excited.
If I
[cheering]
can celebrate it now. Come on now.
You know that thing. Party after party
after party after party. Party after
party. Now there we see you. And to the
glory of God, it's going to be our first
year anniversary after inauguration.
Celebrate. I know you want to go home. I
want to go home too.
Perhaps you don't know why we are
excited and why we are celebrating God.
Please. Where's Where's Emo? Can you
please celebrate my dear associate over
there? I love you. Where's blessing?
Blessing. Say, I see you. I love you. Uh
where's Afalabi?
Always behind all these things you're
saying. Afalabi, God has blessed you and
every of my team. Can we celebrate YCH?
May they see you now? Oh, where are the
other guys?
Hey, Jesus is Lord. I mean I know that
YCHP can be better, but I mean realas
after realas they will fight, they will
they will become friend again. At least
conference have come and gone. H
conference will come and go. Now human
being will remain. So go and men don't
divide.
All right. So OM after party the last
Saturday November. We're going to give
you other details. We are trusting God.
He most likely it's most likely will not
happen in this auditorium because we
want to make it bigger. We'll get you
details. Then the next one, I'm glad to
announce to you that the next pioneers
conference 2027,
it's going to be bigger, better. It's
tagged the foundational blueprint.
You're not excited. [cheering]
So why am I announcing the conference
right now? Of course, according to
instruction, I mean the Holy Spirit's
instruction. And of course, again, I
mean, I'm a man under authority. So we
want to make this meetings bigger and
better. Are we together? Um we had to
start doing installation connect at d
minute and we want to be better at this.
So we want to have a one-year plan by
God's grace. 2027 pioneers conference
foundational blueprint. We want to have
this entire facility shut down. Is it
possible?
>> Talk to me. Is it possible?
>> So making this thing work is is very
simple. We just need to start our
journey from now. So I'm going to do
please do me a favor. Um where is where
is blessing say please don't go too far
I need you around there so that they can
see you let them see you. So quick one
let me announce the third one then I
will now talk about this one then we
close. I'm looking at the timer so I'm
still on time. Then the third one I will
now come back to the conference. The
third one we've not there's no artwork
artwork for it yet but by the grace of
God I know it happened sometimes like
three years ago but it just happened
because I think we c I think it was
kings of supernatural or something but
this time around we want to start
something again I have a mission we as
the king as king we must build from
within
are you ready to hear the announcement
by the grace of God we are starting
Althia K founders league is a football
competition.
You guys like football.
So
I announced to me you not clap reach
this one. It is football night. I
clapping and clapping. We will cancel
it. Don't worry.
So we have because we we are starting I
mean I call it AKL. It's a football
league. It's going to be a football
tournament and we're going to be
involving our installation and it's
there's going to be price tag to it. So
if you like don't get your installation
involved or your So on that part if
you're going to like to be a part of the
football league planning team where's
Caleb?
Caleb where are you? I need you very
fast.
Is my career in this place. Okay. So if
you like to be a part of the plan
because the planning is kicking off
immediately. Caleb let them see your
hand. So please see Caleb immediately
after this meeting. We are kicking off.
Let me for you to know we are serious
about it. There's a pitch we are using
already. I mean the pitch is available
standard pitch for real. So if you like
and I'm trusting God that the first
competition
I'm trusting God though don't let me
announce prize but the winners should be
going home with somewhere around 10 to
20 m.
We are not joking say what pastor said
we are the takeover generation
>> for we we enter every space
enter every space.
So back to the conference matter. So
want to Oh, please can you appreciate
the planning team of this pioneers
conference? Please appreciate them.
Aly led by my darling wife. Where is
she?
[cheering]
Where is my wife now?
I mean
y God
I mean I I
please can you appreciate my wife for
honestly honestly and and the reason I'm
saying this because you know when Bible
says that and God formed Eve out of blah
blah blah he said for helpmate
she's indeed a helpmate I mean I was
able to focus on what matters
my wife telling me yeah she see you know
I'm Yeah, let's go.
Thank you. So, and of course, you know,
every installation rep, thank you so
much. Aquet um I can only mention as I
remember Abig
Alagado Okoba
Abeuta
Island
Church. Aha.
I stress their life. Thank you so much.
Can we please appreciate our pastors
that came all the way from audience?
Thank you. Thank you s Thank you ma and
the beautiful wife of pastor Tumi
King youth church. Can I give you one
secret? Can I give you one secret? Is
only for married people. If you want to
marry quickly, I can connect you to my
spiritual father. I think my spiritual
father is doing something amazing at the
moment. I mean my my oversight. He has
raised me and he's one pastor in church,
pastor Edmund. I watch him like this and
this guy and they marrying some there's
I won't mention but there's one pastor
on my table like this that is marrying
in two weeks time
it's a secret
you imagine
you know you know when secondary school
when somebody fart they say who fart all
of you learn this ah ah
fat yourself all right so quickly back
to the conference conversation So the um
the pioneers conference 2027 we want to
kick off planning immediately like we
only have two weeks rest. So if you're
going to like to be if I not we need as
many people as possible on board. We
need to have a solid team. We are
trusting God that the next conference we
are looking at having 2,000 people in
attendance. Is it possible?
>> Talk to me. Is it possible? So I mean we
need we need I mean our ATP I mean choir
they tried but we need more hands right?
Do you believe that? So we need more
choir members. We need we need ushers.
We need protocols. We need I mean we
need as many people as possible. So if
you would like to work with us and we
are please don't just don't just raise
up your hand because he's sacking you.
You we work you and you will pray
and you will spend your time.
All right. So if you'd like to be a part
of the planning team for 2027 pioneers
conference please um I think you can see
uh blessing where you I'm sorry I'm
delighted everybody say blessing she's
an amazing I mean please appreciate
blessing for me
this is a person
she's the one that when we give her
budget you say no no no
it's so she will if you carry budget go
it's not knife is sword you will slash
she has been amazing with the church
finance. Thank you so much. Thank you.
Blessing. Thank you. She's she's not
looking at when we are doing spirit she
would ah but when it's financing PMI no
no no no no no no we don't have the
money for that. I'll be like ah but
thank God for people like that. If not
ah it is well. So if you like to be a
part of the next planning team please
say blessing. Let's build a solid team.
Are we together? Let's build the youth
church. Can we rise up on our feet as we
close? Please see her now and I would
like to see people turn up for it. I
think we're kicking off land
immediately. I want to have an amazing
conference in 2027 and possibly 2027
conference might be a two-day conference
and it might be a camp meeting, a
convention. It's a big meeting. The way
the way God is showing me, we might be
locking down almost all the um what do
they call that thing? Small
somebody bought me that word. All those
lodge it's not hotel short. Yeah. All
the short left we have. God just show me
that. I know it's possible, but we need
to plan it ahead. Are we together?
Somebody say, "Father, we thank you."
>> Say, "Father, we thank you."
Say, "Father, we thank you."
>> Father, we thank you.
>> Can we say this? I say, "God is
exalted."
>> You're not. Say, "God is exalted."
>> The devil is defeated.
>> Jesus is Lord. And I am a pioneer.
Somebody say, "God is exalted." The
devil is defeated.
Jesus is Lord and I am bringing
solutions to my space.
So for the last time say God is exalted.
The devil is defeated.
Jesus is Lord. I am the light of the
world. Can we take our greed as we go?
Let's do it together. Can we come
together in the middle? Don't worry.
Let's come together. I want us to take
that grid. Can I have a camera on us
here? one of the cameras very fast
please let's come together now we are I
wish we know that soon we are one body
one spirit bound together by God's love
we sharing one
to do
we [music] ah don't forget so natural
hey king
somebody say King's word found.
We are We ARE WE ARE WE ARE We are the
King's World.
We are We are We are one body. We are We
ARE SOMEBODY SAY, "HEY, WE are we
[music] are we are one body." Say
very simple. Hey, we are we are we are
one body.
We are we are we are one body.
We are we are we are we are
we are we are we are we are we are
[music]
we are we are we are we are we are we
are we are we are
we are we are we are we are oh
we are we are we are we are we are we
are one body
We are we are we are we are one body.
[music]
We are we are oh we are we are oh oh
it's your energy that will determine HOW
TO GO WE ARE OH we are we are oh oh
just repeat it now we are we are we are
we are one body
family
we are Kings word family. [music] Kings
word family that's we are saved.
Hey Jesus family that's we are saved.
I am king.
[music]
Let's come together. I want us to take
decreed. Are we ready?
The camera can come to the front. The
one you are moving. Go.
Ah. Don't be doing like this to us now.
Somebody come and mount phone for me.
You cannot you cannot keep my side. You
can can we come together? I want us take
that creek together. Oh, okay. That's
true. Let's come together. Yeah. Let's
come and face camera.
Woo. [screaming] Don't worry. There's a
screen in front of you.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. This camera. Yeah. Now,
let's come together. Let's come
together. Come come come. Why you
running? Huh?
Wait, come to the front.
Why you running from? Body does not run
from body.
Everybody aside the person behind the
camera, they are done for the day. I
hope that camera can see me well enough.
Are we ready? At the count of three. AO.
Come on. Come on. Come. I need here. At
the count of three. Please give me that
creed. Who giving us the creed? We know
it. Abby, are you ready? One. Let me
come to the front. Oh, you cannot. You
cannot take my shine. I am I am the
youth pastor of this church.
Are we ready?
>> At a count of three.
>> At a count of three. 1 2 3. With all of
your energy, I am King's word. I have no
taste for me religion without change. I
live a RESULTORIENTED PURPOSE-DRIVEN
LIFE based on principles in God's word.
I'm a man of the word yielded to the
spirit. I'M COMMITTED TO GOD'S purpose
for my life. I take my place in
and his agenda for the earth and might.
Let's go.
>> Let's go.
>> Yeah.
Ah. Ah.
>> WHO ARE WE? [music]
AND I LOVE THIS.
[cheering]
>> We are.
[music]
All right.
Please look at me.
We are Don't worry. We are going. We are
done. Um,
okay. I think there's no other thing,
right?
All right. Thank you so much. I'll see
you at Owenbe the after party. God bless
you.